Yui?
Yui, you in there?
Do you have a toothache or something?
Well, if you're not gonna drink it...
That's not it.
I was just thinking about
my brother's show the other day...
The two clock hands overlap
tokei no hari ga futatsu majiwaru
Heralding the dawn...
aratanaru sekai ga...
Oh yeah, wasn't WITH's show cool?
Wait.
Your brother's?
Did you just say it was your brother's?
You heard right!
Shougo, who kicked me off stage – he's my brother!
Is he a dreamless jerk, or what!
But... he helped you, right?
He dreamed what now?
I guess you don't really get along...
I won't quit till we're a hundred times
dreamier and more popular than BoyPara!
Then I guess we've gotta
get more girls interested in PriPara,
so more of them start coming to PriPara!
We have to shout from the rooftops
how amazing PriPara is.
"From the rooftops"...
Puni?
That sounds dreamtastic.
And how do we do that?
Well, what if we ran a show on PriPara TV
promoting Paparajuku's PriPara?
Wow! That dreams my socks off!
Doesn't it?
Yeah!
Hello, Lala capiscing.
Long time no see.
Sophie!
Sophie's Come to Cool!
PriPara Pukuoka Branch
Mirei called me earlier.
She said you were working hard in Paparajuku,
so I thought I should come and see you too.
You're coming to visit? That sounds great!
Did you say Sophie? As in Houjou Sophie?
That super cool, natural-born prodigy idol,
with the star designer sister
and whose "little birds" get joy or sorrow from –
that Sophie?
Yes, that's me.
She's a member of SoLaMi SMILE
and a Divine Idol just like me!
A Divine Idol...
Hey, I just dreamed up a great idea!
We should Sophie to put on a dreamy-cool show
in the PriPara feature programme!
With a Divine Idol on board,
no one'll be able to dream their eyes off us!
I'm a Divine Idol here too, you know...
Oh, right.
I'm not sure I caught all that, but it sounds fun.
All right!
But isn't it kind of far
from the Pukuoka section to here?
Will your stamina last?
It's fine!
I've got a little bird with me.
What little bird?
It's the shoebill!
That's perfect, then.
Capisce please! Capisce please! Capisce please!
Dreamy-cute please!
Dreamy-cute please! Dreamy-cute please!
A programme to promote Paparajuku's PriPara, you say?
We have to do this to dream up
people's PriPara dreams!
And Sophie's coming from the Pukuoka branch.
I'm sure it'll go over huge!
Very well.
Really?
The studio's free all day tomorrow,
so I'll book you in for a twenty-four hour slot!
Hey – wait, no! We don't need that much time!
Three hours would be plenty!
I see.
I've slotted you in for three hours after school tomorrow.
We've gotta make this a ton of fun
and get everyone to watch!
Yep!
Dreamy-Cute
Notebook
Okay, I'm gonna think up some segments for the show!
Dreamy-Cute
Notebook
School word chain! "After school", "lesson", "nightmare" –
no, that doesn't count!
Make sure you check out PriPara TV today.
Thank you very much!
Yui!
Whatcha doing?
Pripara
I ntrodu cto ry
F e at u r e
With
Special Guest
Sophie
Today
Pripara
I ntrodu cto ry
F e at u r e
With
Special Guest
Sophie
Today
Pripara
I ntrodu cto ry
F e at u r e
With
Special Guest
Sophie
Today
Pripara
I ntrodu cto ry
F e at u r e
With
Special Guest
Sophie
Today
Pripara
I ntrodu cto ry
F e at u r e
With
Special Guest
Sophie
Today
Pripara
I ntrodu cto ry
F e at u r e
With
Special Guest
Sophie
Today
Pripara
I ntrodu cto ry
F e at u r e
With
Special Guest
Sophie
Today
Pripara
I ntrodu cto ry
F e at u r e
With
Special Guest
Sophie
Today
Pripara
I ntrodu cto ry
F e at u r e
With
Special Guest
Sophie
Today
Pripara
I ntrodu cto ry
F e at u r e
With
Special Guest
Sophie
Today
Pripara
I ntrodu cto ry
F e at u r e
With
Special Guest
Sophie
Today
Here, take one!
Pripara
I ntrodu cto ry
F e at u r e
With
Special Guest
Sophie
Today
With
I ntrodu cto ry
F e at u r e
P
V
Today
I ntrodu cto ry
F e at u r e
With
Sophie
Today
PriPara
I ntrodu cto ry
F e at u r e
With
Special Guest
Sophie
Today
We're doing a show to drum up interest in PriPara!
The Divine Idol Sophie's gonna perform as well!
Yeah?
I guess we'll check it out, then.
Looking forward to it!
Thank you capisce!
Nino, you should check it out too.
No way! That's my jogging time!
And if it rains, I do pushups.
Even though the Divine Idol Sophie's gonna be there...
Oh well. We'll just have to keep putting the word out.
No matter where you Ji-go-ku...
There she is again!
the walls and the doors both have ears.
Jigoku Mimiko stands before you.
Putting what word out?
U-Um...
I believe the words "Divine Idol" drifted into my ears...
Y-You must have been hearing things...
Gunk in your ear or something.
Waxy, slimy, SoLaMi SMILE...
I'll sniff your little plans out, mark my words.
You wanna do something later?
It's about to start.
Yep.
What's a-bab-out to start, now?
Is something going to be on the television?
Oh, well...
Hey, what we do? She'll find out
Yui and Lala are gonna be on TV!
Ah!
Oh, that's the stuff!
That's right, there's a ba-BoyPara show on today!
Actually, I just recalled some
bab-usiness I have to attend to.
I've got to get back to my room before it ba-begins!
That was close! Nicely done, Hana!
It's bang on starting time!
Today we have a special programme for you!
We hope you'll have a wonderful time!
Yui...
and Lala's...
Dream Special!
Dreamy
Dreamy Dreamy Dream Special!
Dream Special!
Yay! We're finally underway!
Puni!
I can't take the anticipation!
Announce
title!
has arrived
Announce
title!
Miss Sophie
has arrived
And hey! It seems our super
amazing guest has just arrived!
If I'm dreaming, don't wake me!
Now then, I wonder which
big guest has come to visit today!
Our viewer ratings are skyrocketing!
Our special guest...
is Sophie!
What?
It's the shoebill...
with no Sophie!
Don't tell me...
Sophie didn't fall off, did she?
Pushu...
Punicorn!
Puni.
Dream, dream, dream, dream...
Sophie must have got lost on the way here!
I'll go and look for her.
Hold on.
I'm more dreamy-familiar with these parts, so I'll go!
I dreamed up a whole bunch of segments
for the show in here, so keep it rolling along!
Dream like the wind!
Not bad at all!
Capisce!
Puni! Puni!
Hey, wait!
I'm all by myself?
Puni!
Now our viewer ratings are plummeting!
Punicorn!
So Yui, what was your first impression of Sophie?
Dreamy-cute!
And dreamy-amazing!
I was, uh, dreamy-amazed!
How about that, Sophie?
Okay, my little birds.
This is just a shambles.
Let's go watch BoyPara in our room.
Yeah, let's do it!
Who's your number one in WITH?
Mm, it's gotta be Asahi.
Koyoi for me!
Sophie!
Where the dream are you?
Sophie?
Pochi's House
Where are you?
Sophie...
Pushu!
Dream?
Pushu...
What the dream?
What happened to her?
Um...
Are you dreaming okay there?
I don't suppose you dreamed
a glimpse of Sophie around here?
Pushu...
She's all dreamy-cool,
kinda like... this, you know?
Pushu...
I guess not.
Dreamscuse me, then...
Red...
Flash...
Hm?
Red Flash...
Red panda?
Paparajuku Zoo
Look, look! Red pandas, you guys!
They're so cute!
Red Flash...
I'm a red panda!
Let's be friends!
Red pandas are a hundred times
cuter than normal pandas,
a thousand times cuter than racoons,
faster runners than dogs
and can fly higher than crows!
And here's my buddy Lala!
What? I'm a red panda too now?
Huh? How'd you dream your way here, Lala?
Lick, lick.
Red Flash...
Ah, lick, lick.
What about PriPara TV?
No! Lala's supposed to be at PriPara TV.
That's right – I have to hurry!
Please accept my dreampologies, but I have to go.
I'm looking for Sophie, you see.
I'm Sophie, I'm lost...
You want fairy floss?
Red Flash...
I want fairy floss!
Me too!
Thanks fer comin'!
I want a Yui one!
She's so cute!
I don't want Lala.
Sit tight – Yui fairy floss comin' up!
I'm Sophie, I'm lost...
Here ya go!
Yay! Thank you!
I'm Sophie, I'm lost...
I'm so fairy lost...
You're what?
Ah, I was daydreaming again!
What do I do?
I can't leave her like this...
I'm Sophie, I'm lost...
The tickets in our hearts,
Snapped in two,
In that moment...
I have an update for you.
That shining future opened before us
Our viewer ratings have dropped
from 31% at the start down to 7% just now!
I love you!
This is bad!
I've gotta switch to a new plan!
I – friend – you...
Puni-puni!
Puni, punicorn.
Dreamy-Cute
Notebook
Pu...
Dreamy-Cute
Notebook
Let's see, let's see...
Dreamy-Cute
Notebook
What's this?
Dreamy-Cute
Notebook
Whip up a hundred rice balls and eat ten of them...
Dreamy-Cute
Notebook
Cooking made simple: making smoked pickles
the easy way with Cooky...
Dreamy-Cute
Notebook
What the heck? I can't do this stuff!
Dreamy-Cute
Notebook
Our ratings have just hit 5%!
Dreamy-Cute
Notebook
Oh no! Um, um...
Dual
cup-and-ball
Dance with a
dreamy smile
Dual
cup-and-ball
Dance with a
dreamy smile
Dual
cup-and-ball
Dance with a
dreamy smile
Dual
cup-and-ball
Dance with a
dreamy smile
Dual
cup-and-ball
Dance with a
dreamy smile
Dual
cup-and-ball
Dance with a
dreamy smile
Dual
cup-and-ball
Dance with a
dreamy smile
Dual
cup-and-ball
Dance with a
dreamy smile
Dual
cup-and-ball
Dance with a
dreamy smile
Dual
cup-and-ball
Dance with a
dreamy smile
Dual
cup-and-ball
Dance with a
dreamy smile
Dual
cup-and-ball
Dance with a
dreamy smile
Dual
cup-and-ball
Dance with a
dreamy smile
Dual
cup-and-ball
Dance with a
dreamy smile
Dual
cup-and-ball
Dance with a
dreamy smile
Dual
cup-and-ball
Dance with a
dreamy smile
Dual
cup-and-ball
Dance with a
dreamy smile
Dual
cup-and-ball
Dance with a
dreamy smile
Okay! I'm sure I can do this!
Punicorn!
And here we go...
Dual cup-and-ball!
And now a word from our sponsors!
After the break: Will the big guest finally appear?
Pushu...
Ugh...
Where are you, Sophie?
Pushu...
Lala won't last much longer at this rate...
Sneak, sneak... whoosh!
I've lain in wait for you!
That person must be the Divine Idol you spoke of.
Divine Idol? This girl?
Pushu?
Are we looking at the same person?
Even if you deceive my eyes, my ears will uncover...
Pushu...
You speak truly.
I hear it clear as day, from the bottom
of my ears that she is not a Divine Idol.
Then where is this Divine Idol?
That's what I want to know.
I can't take this anymore!
Lala, I'm sorry!
Yo, whatcha doing down there?
Nino?
Thanks a dream, Nino.
No problemo.
I can just make it part of my workout – no biggie at all!
So how far d'ya want me to carry you?
I have to look for Sophie...
But I'm sure Lala can't keep it up much longer.
Could you take us to Prism Stone for now?
Prism Stone?
It's where you go to be an idol.
Hm? All right, you got it!
Hup, two, three! Hup, two, three...
Yay yay
Matchi
And now for our next feature:
Yay yay
Matchi
Matching Meganees!
Yay yay
Matchi
Yay yay
Matchi
Yay yay
Matchi
Yay yay
Matchi
Let's try this Meganee...
Mega.
and this one!
Yay, they match!
Next I'll try...
Hm, which one do I pick now...
This Meganee...
It's the system!
...and this one!
All right, lucky me!
By the way, our viewer ratings are plummeting further!
This is lame.
I've had enough.
Let's go back to our rooms.
Yeah, let's go.
Cooking completed.
I must have switched on Cooky's rapid cooking mode button when I was in a dreamy hurry earlier.
Do you want some too, Nino?
No thanks, I'm in the middle of a workout.
Then I'll make one for Miss Pushu here.
But I made one just for me out of reflex!
Wait just a moment.
Pushu...
There we go.
Red Flash...
I knew you'd be hungry.
Here you go.
Here's a sour plum one.
Pushu...
Just the plum?
Oh, that shoebill of mine.
What a pickle she's got me into,
dropping me off halfway like that.
S-Sophie?
Why are you...?
Thanks for the Red Flash.
You must be Yui.
I've heard all about you from Lala.
Things seem shipshape here.
This here Nino's gonna get back to jogging.
Thank you, Nino!
We should get going too.
Yeah!
Wait – we've really gotta get dreaming!
Nothing's going to get in my way now.
She's so dreamy-cool!
You are frozen in place.
You will not move away from the television.
I'm gonna go back to my room, okay?
The power to move is leaving your body...
We sorta have to watch, don't we?
Now you're unable to even lift your arm...
Yeah... though I can feel my strength fading.
Another 0.1% of the viewership has disappeared.
Hey, I said don't move! Keep watching the TV!
Lala, you don't need to try so hard. Really.
It's hard enough for us to just watch.
Wait up, Sophie!
You bet.
Hey, did you see that girl just now?
She was so pretty!
If your interests are piqued,
come on and follow me, my little birds.
She's so cool!
So cool!
Welcome, Miss Sophie the Divine Idol.
Divine Idol?
Miss Lala's waiting for you.
She's a Divine Idol!
I know.
Oh, just a moment, please.
Here's the hottest new item in Paparajuku:
your Idol Watch!
Idol Watch?
It's the system here!
Well, ladies.
Are you ready?
Sure am!
PriPara Change!
Amazing!
This is really me?
This is so cute!
I might get start getting hit on!
You look splendid, my little birds.
Sophie!
I've been waiting for you!
Long time no see, Lala.
I'm so glad we made it.
Thanks for keeping the show rolling, Lala.
Yeah... I got through it somehow...
Say, Lala, aren't you smaller than usual?
Well, it's a long story...
Well, then.
I can't keep you little birds watching
waiting much longer, can I?
After bringing these girls to PriPara,
Sophie's Idol Time has been maxed out.
She can now give a three-minute performance!
Scan the appropriate number
of My Tickets for your outfit.
You can also scan each other's Friend Tickets.
Countdown to Idol Time!
Miss Sophie's colour is a cool purple.
Miss Sophie's favourite is the outfit
with the S initial ribbon emblem.
Happy Emblem Berry Ensemble!
Start!
Lady Sophie, you're sparkling!
Even if you get lost on occasion,
don't you want to walk your own path?
My little birds,
let me give you the pleasure
of entering PriPara for the first time.
So cool!
Now, break out of the birdcage
saa torikago nante breakout
Revolution: Red Flash! (Flash!)
kakumei no red flash (flash)
Take a look around
sonna semai sekai de
Do you think you can spread your wings
habatakeru to
In a world so confined?
omotteru no
"Tomorrow it starts for real"?
ashita kara honki tte
Well, that won't do
dame ne
You'll never reach the sky, you'll never fly
toberu sora ga nai wa
Isn't she the girl I carried before?
Let it shine out of the darkness
uchuu wo tsukuru big bang wo
Like the Big Bang itself
okosu kurai
Set your feelings ablaze and burn with a Red Flash!
atsui omoi wo hora moyashite red flash
Get ready?
get ready
So feel, so feel, so feel, so feel free to be free, girls!
so feel so feel so feel so feel free to free girls
Come liberate yourselves! (Red Flash!)
kaihou shichainasai (red flash)
Save your fantasies for later
amai kuusou sore ja no no
My little birds
kotorichan-tachi
This ruby-red fruit holds a spark (Red Flash!)
akai shoudou no mi ga (red flash)
Inflaming instincts deep within
doukasen nano yo
The instant it touches your lips
kuchibiru ni fureta
You'll feel a Red Flash! (Liberation Rouge!)
shunkan ni red flash (liberation rouge)
Now, break out of the birdcage
saa torikago nante breakout
Revolution: Red Flash! (Flash!)
kakumei no red flash (flash)
Making Drama, switch on!
Rain...
Look up at the sky...
and smile!
Just believe!
just believe
You know in your heart that you can do it
sorosoro shinjite agenakya
Have faith in yourself
anata jishin wo
Hello!
Everyone has wings of their own
dare ni datte hane ga atte
Blue-sky Smile Sparkling!
Anyone can take flight
sora wo toberu no
Cyalume Time!
Get ready?
get ready
So feel, so feel, so feel, so feel free to be free, girls!
so feel so feel so feel so feel free to free girls
Liberate yourselves and you'll see (Red Flash!)
kaihou shichau nara (red flash)
You can unleash all your roiling passions too
atsui kanjou tokihanatte
My little birds
kotorichan-tachi
It's a Super Cyalume Ensemble!
This ruby-red fruit holds a spark (Red Flash!)
akai shoudou no mi ga (red flash)
Inflaming instincts deep within
doukasen nano yo
The instant it touches your lips
kuchibiru ni fureta
You'll feel the Red Flash (Liberation Rouge)
shunkan ni red flash (liberation rouge)
Now, break out of the birdcage
saa torikago nante breakout
Revolution: Red Flash! (Flash!)
kakumei no red flash (flash)
Liberate yourselves!
kaihou shichae
Now seize your freedom and break out
saa jiyuu ni natte breakout
Revolution: Red Flash!
kakumei no red flash
Magnificent as always, Miss Sophie!
I love you, Lady Sophie!
Congratulations!
Miss Sophie has received
a new Super Cyalume Ensemble!
I pledge my life to Lady Sophie!
Incidentally, our viewership
skyrocketed at the end to 75%!
Your performance was dreamcredible, Sophie!
So that "Red Flash" thing turned out to be a sour plum.
When Sophie's out of stamina,
she pops one in and becomes the cool Sophie again!
She seems kinda deflated now though.
Was I able to help you two?
You bet! Thanks a bunch, Sophie!
That's good.
There.
Come on, Yui.
Lala here and I are gonna keep dreaming our best!
Capisce!
Well, I have to head back to Pukuoka.
See you later, Sophie.
Thanks again, Sophie!
Goodbye!
Pushu.
Next Episode
We're gonna make this event a hit!
But first we need a dreamload more idols to debut!
Capisce!
And I know just the girl to recruit.
Me too, me too!
Nijiiro Nino!
No marks!
Nino here's only interested in sports!
Say what? But being an idol's like a dream – it's so fun!
We'll just have to teach you how fun idoling really is!
Next time, Aim for the Rice!
Aim for the Rice!
Come on, everyone! It's time to be an idol!