Darn it!
I'll catch it!
We'll win! And then I'll take Nino
to the Idol Time Grand Prix
and we'll enter together!
I caught it!
You're out!
Oh no!
It really hurts!
Slug It!
The Idol Time Grand Prix!
Ji... go... ku...
Inning
Team Name
Three outs! Change!
Yui! Is your ankle okay?
You bet! Right as dream!
Like heck it is!
Come on, let me see.
It's fine, it's fine.
I've got my dream power, after all.
What's that supposed to be?
Whenever I'm in trouble, I just believe in dreams
and it gives me incredible amounts of power!
That's dream power!
Yeah, I ain't buying a word of that.
What? That's a dreamy shock!
You should work on finding
your own wonderful dream, Nino.
We don't have time for your "dreamy dream" stuff!
We'll be fine! Go over to the sickbay
and get some first aid!
But I just told you – I have my dream power, so I'm fine.
No marks! I ain't buying it!
Nino doesn't believe a word of what I'm dreaming.
Yui!
I'm here to get you!
It's time for you to enter the Grand Prix!
What, already?
That's right. Maybe if I can just show her
the power of my performance...
Here, Lala, take this!
Huh?
A mitt?
Wait, you're still in the bottom of the fifth?
And you're losing twelve runs to nine?
Sorry! It's up to you now, Lala!
I'm off now!
Yo, be careful!
And get that ankle looked at soon!
Strike! You're out!
Manaka!
Thank you so much for filling in for us!
You're a lifesaver!
We're only down three points –
we'll catch up in no time!
After all, we've got Nino on our side!
Well, sure, but...
You should work on finding
your own wonderful dream, Nino.
A dream...
Did I ever have a dream?
Strike!
No, I kinda feel like I had
a real big dream when I was a kid...
Strike two!
Argh, but I can't remember it at all!
Strike! You're out!
What? She got struck out?
The Head Disciplinarian really gets under your skin,
and Nijiiro can't carry the team,
so her confidence is shot.
And then Yumekawa overdid it
and got her ankle injured,
Wha– Yui hurt her ankle?
Oh, man...
The show and the game are total no-gos.
That's why I told Yui to go to the sickbay.
Owie-ow...
Gotta run gently...
Yumekawa!
Whatever happened to your ankle?
I, uh, twisted it before...
That's a ba-big deal!
A lady shouldn't let her leg be sullied by a ba-bruise!
You have to get some first aid on the double ba-bubble!
Oh, um, yes...
That's why...
I'm going to the sickbay right now!
Nino...
I've never seen her without a confident smile on her face.
This is nothing compared to what she's going through!
Besides, I have the Divine Idol Lala on my side!
Let's go for it, Yui!
Even if she's not all that dependable sometimes...
I'm not injured at all!
You see, when I was but a child, I was turned into a cyborg
by the evil organisation Gorgonzola
and my ankles were transformed into steel!
Miss Manager?
Puni...
Is Miss Yui not here yet?
Pu...
If she doesn't take the stage
before the current performance ends,
we'll have to close off entries!
Puni!
You can do it!
Okonomiyaki
Ninja-
Monja
Heck yeah, all sold out!
Was that Lala's voice just now?
Strike!
You're out!
That's two out!
Well, this is just embarrassing to watch!
Dorothy? Reona?
Looks like you could use a helpin' hand or two!
I'll do my best!
One more out and it's game over.
I can see our team's victory clear as day.
Meaning...
The Grand Prix will end in failure
when it can't muster even two competitors,
meaning...
Paparajuku's PriPara, the root of all evil...
Well, we'll all have to bid farewell to it, won't we?
Whatcha laughing at?
You couldn't hit the broad side of a barn!
Curses! When did you get there?
Hey, hey!
You couldn't throw a party, pitcher!
I may have let my guard down... but no more.
I will now bring an end to PriPara!
Whoa, her eyes have Hell's fury itself in them...
Lala!
Hit it like "Ca... pi... sce"!
Like... Capi!
...sce.
Did he tell you to swing on "pi", ya dummy?
Jeez!
I'm sorry!
But this time!
Here's...
Ca...
pi...
sce!
Nice one, Lala!
Oops-a-daisy!
Ji... go... ku!
It's the last inning. Two outs, bases loaded.
This is gonna decide the match.
You're just a frog in a well,
knowing nothing of the great ocean.
She's right.
I've been riding on my small goals
and petty wins this whole time.
A dream...
C'mon, get it together over there!
Hey, it's from Yui.
No communication during a match!
Sorry! I capisce!
But I want to call a time out!
Nino, watch this!
What's goin' on?
Yui just messaged me to say
to get a TV since her show's starting!
What?
Puni!
Punicorn!
Scan the appropriate number
of My Tickets for your outfit.
You can also scan each other's Friend Tickets.
Countdown to Idol Time!
Yui's competing in her first Grand Prix
with her favourite outfit
from the brand she designed herself, Fantasy Time!
Magical Star Pink Ensemble!
Start!
Now we're cooking!
Look, it's starting!
Hey, who's she?
What's going on here?
Hello there! I'm Yumekawa Yui!
Yumekawa!
Standing here on this stage
has been my dream for so long!
At first the audience
was just a bunch of Meganees,
but even so,
even when I had setbacks
and things didn't go how I'd hoped,
I kept believing in my dreams,
and that's why I'm here today!
I want to send my feelings out
to my beloved and bedreamed friends!
Please listen! This is my dream concert!
Baba-ree-woo!
She's ba-burdened by injury!
There will be no dream concert!
I have a duty to protect my students.
I will ba-bar this foolishness, mark my words!
Tick-tock magicalun-lun - Idol Time starts now!
chikutaku magica runrun aidoru taimu sutaato
Come on!
kamon
(Magical! Idol! Here we go!)
(majikaru aidoru here we go)
It's the magic girls long for
onna no ko ga akogaretekita mahou
A splendorous world where mysteries abound
fushigi wa joushiki chouisekai
Baba! Baba! Baba!
I cast my spell and it's showtime
tonaetara shoutaimu
I'd better hurry up, cause everyone's waiting - no, no more limits
sore ja isogou minna matteru kitto anrimiteddo
Now the future is boundless
saa mirai eigou
Halt this, halt it now!
Mark this moment in time!
toki o kizamu yo
I will ba-bar this performance!
(Tick-tock magical go!)
(chikutaku magikaru go)
Don't interrupt the cook cycle!
Now hold on just a moment? I can't stop! Here, with my mic in hand
chotto jasutamoomen tomaranai yo maiku katate ni
Interfering with a show is against the rules-pri!
Excuse me! It is not a matter of rules!
I will not permit her to perform on an injured ankle!
Taking the hour hand and dancing, my heart singing
tanshin to dancing kokoro singing
In a thrilling singularity
tokimeki shingyuraritii
She's injured?
Yui pri-clared it herself – this show is her dream!
The mystery of the unclear is so entrancing
katachi no nai mono koso itsudatte hoshii yo
We have to watch her until the end-pri!
Music holds my hopes, so pretty and sweet
kibou to myuujikku puriti kyuuti
When I'm so excited I can't hold still
dokidoki machikirenai nara
Tick-tock magicalun-lun - it's Idol Time, and we're not done!
chikutaku magica runrun aidoru taimu tsuzuku yo
I just believe in my dreams
and it gives me incredible amounts of power!
You should work on finding
your own wonderful dream, Nino.
Yui...
She's not slowing down at all, even with her injury!
With my dream power, I'll be right as rain!
Lost in karma and I don't know what to do
nayuta setsuna fuan da yo
Am I just a second from tumbling into the abyss?
ichibyougo wa naraku no soko
I want to find my dream too!
You'll find it, I'm sure of it!
You've just gotta keep believing in yourself
sonna toki wa jibun shinjite
Making Drama, switch on!
Start off allegro, and then vivace
areguro soshite vivaache
There's the most beauty in the now
toki yo nanji mo utsukushii
Like a dream, dreamy-cute!
Is it a dream or reflection, truth or illusion? Who can say?
yume ka utsusu ka uso ka hontou ka dare mo wakaranai
Whee!
Adrift in the ebb and flow of time and space
watashi dake jikan fuuyuu kuukan
Until eternal twilight blooms
towairaito ga terasu made
It's dreamcredible: welcome to dreamland!
Tick-tock super Idol Time!
chikutaku super idol time
Tick and tock and
chii-ku ta-ku
Dreamy-cute Magical Clock Land!
Now just a moment, I hold my secrets always in my heart
jasutamoomen zutto zutto himitsu o mune ni
In the loveliest outfit, in a single breath
saikou no koode wanburesu de
What drives her to try so hard with that ba-burden?
Awakened by dream energy
mezameru doriimu enajii
The mystery of the unclear is so entrancing
katachi no nai mono koso itsudatte hoshii yo
Cyalume Time!
The mystery of the unclear is so entrancing
katachi no nai mono koso itsudatte hoshii yo
Music holds my hopes, so pretty and sweet
kibou to myuujikku puriti kyuuti
When I'm so excited I can't hold still
dokidoki machikirenai nara
Dreamy-cute!
Tick tock, I've gotta take it
chikutaku ima toraete
That chance comes just the once!
chansu wa isshun dake yo
Tick-tock magicalun-lun, now Idol Time: da capo!
chikutaku magica runrun aidoru taimu da kaapo
Yui's giving it all she's got!
So I've gotta do the same!
I'm hitting this!
That's game!
Avocado Academy's Softball Club
wins thirteen to twelve!
Yo, we did it! We did it!
Owie-ow...
I'm all out of dream power!
Well done!
Nurse Sophie will see you now.
Yo, we did it! We did it!
Let's get going! Yui's waiting for us at the stage!
You got it!
You think I'm letting you go?
What?
We'll hold her back for ya!
So get going!
Ji... go... ku!
Go for it with an all-out dash!
Heh.
I owe ya one!
Five minutes until the entries close.
If we don't receive at least two entrants,
the Idol Time Grand Prix,
currently in progress, will be invalidated.
Please do hurry!
Cheers!
Here you go, all fixed up!
Yay!
Pushu!
It's dreamed up good as new!
Thank you, Sophie!
Nino! Lala!
The game's all won.
All thanks to that courageous show ya put on!
Yui! Is your ankle okay after dancing so hard on it?
We were all really worried about you!
My dream power sent all the pain flying away!
Hey, don't go nuts there.
But I gotta say cheers!
I reckon your performance gave me more power too!
Wow, really?
Please do hurry!
I'm off!
Chuppe!
So that's what it was all about!
What ba-beautiful courage!
Chuppe... Chuppe!
Scan the appropriate number
of My Tickets for your outfit.
You can also scan each other's Friend Tickets.
Countdown to Idol Time!
With baseball balls and gloves incorporated as a motif,
it's the sportiest outfit in all of PriPara!
Baseball Game Ensemble!
Startin'!
Puni-puni!
Gleaming steaming fresh!
Helter-skelter - ready, go!
accha koccha ready go
Come on!
come on
Play ball!
play ball
Now it's summer, summertime, she who moves first strikes a hit tune
summer summer summertime sente hisshou hitto chuun
Here come the helper, ready to rumble
sukketo sanjou kokkara ga honban da
I'm gonna be number one, and you can bet I'll walk the walk
number number number one mezasou yuugen jikkou
I pick up the rhythm and then it's one, two, three and
rizumu wo kanjitottara isseeno de
Commands input straight into my heart, now I'm ready, go
kokoro komando nyuuryoku wo ready go
Circle, cross, triangle, I'll square with you, so mark my words
maru batsu sankaku shikaku sankaku
There's no need to get marked off
sanka shikaku da nante no iranai yo
'Cause when you're here, we're all friends
koko ni kitara minna tomodachi
Good fences make good neighbours ('Sup!)
shitashiki naka de atte mo reigi wo (chassu)
And you gotta respect both friends and rivals (Let's go!)
mikata ni mo teki ni mo keii wo haraou (sharassu)
You know if you hold back (If you hold back?)
tekagen shitara (shitara)
You're disqualified (You're out!)
sokkoku taijou (auto)
Here I come, with my full power
zenryoku de iku yo saa
So see if you can keep up
kakugo kimete tsuikite ne
Three, two, one... go!
three two one go
It's helter-skelter! Get up, get up and play the game!
whoa accha koccha get up get up play the game
You're dancing before you even realise
karada ga katte ni odoridashite
Out of control, no slowing down
seigyo fukanou tomerarenai yo
Our strategy's going by instinct
senryaku wa mochiron kankaku
It's helter-skelter! Get up, get up and play the game!
accha koccha get up get up purei the game
Here I come!
Glitch out all your wimpiness (Hop to it!)
okubyou na jibun wo bagurasechatte (ikkee)
Making Drama, switch on!
My heart's pounding so much it feels like it'll burst
bakubaku takanatta kono mune no naka nara
Beep-boop!
The signal's all scrambled up (Yay!)
sukuranburu joutai (yay)
Comin' at ya!
Live it up! This rocks!
live it up saikou jan
Let's play Idol Time!
let's play idol time
Yeah, come on now and ride that player's high
whoa motto motto zutto zutto player's high
Feel like shouting it right from the heart
hontou no kimochi ga sakebigoe
Poppin' Bit Scramble!
We'll be earnest, burning with ardour
shoujiki ni narou atsukunarou yo
That's how it's gotta be for me
watashi nara mochiron
I'm havin' a blast, yo!
That's a high score!
Helter-skelter - ready, go!
accha koccha ready go
It's helter-skelter! Get up, get up and play the game!
whoa accha koccha get up get up play the game
Cyalume Time!
You're dancing before you even realise
karada ga katte ni odoridashite
Out of control, no slowing down
seigyo fukanou tomerarenai yo
Our strategy's going by instinct
senryaku wa mochiron kankaku
Full marks!
It's helter-skelter! Get up, get up and play the game!
accha koccha get up get up purei the game
Glitch out all your wimpiness (Hop to it!)
okubyou na jibun wo bagurasechatte (ikkee)
My heart's pounding so much it feels like it'll burst
bakubaku takanatta kono mune no naka nara
The signal's all scrambled now (Yay!)
sukuranburu joutai (yay)
Live it up! This rocks!
live it up saikou jan
Let's play Idol Time!
let's play idol time
Nino, full marks and bonus points!
Perfect marks!
Ba-brilliant...
Now then!
It's time for the results!
Let's find out who the winner
of the first-ever Idol Time Grand Prix is!
Wha– Grand Prix?
Yo, this was a competition?
What's this? What...
What's happening?
It's Super Idol Time!
Welcome to the temporal paradise, the Time Garden!
What's your name?
My name is...
Tick-tock super Idol Time!
chikutaku super idol time
Falala!
Tick and tock and
chii-ku ta-ku
This time is filled with dreams!
Now just a moment, I hold my secrets always in my heart
jasutamoomen zutto zutto himitsu o mune ni
Take the Idol Time Harp!
In the loveliest outfit, in a single breath
saikou no koode wanburesu de
Now the Idol Time Mic...
...is complete!
Awakened by dream energy
mezameru doriimu enajii
The mystery of the unclear is so entrancing
katachi no nai mono koso itsudatte hoshii yo
Now, let time sparkle!
The Dream Cyalume!
Music holds my hopes, so pretty and sweet
kibou to myuujikku puriti kyuuti
When I'm so excited I can't hold still
dokidoki machikirenai nara
Tick tock, I've gotta take it
chikutaku ima toraete
That chance comes just the once!
chansu wa isshun dake yo
Tick-tock magicalun-lun, now Idol Time: da capo!
chikutaku magica runrun aidoru taimu da kaapo
Now, come this way!
An Idol Time Ensemble for you!
Take the Hair Accessory of Time!
Thank you for a splendid time!
Yui, congratulations on winning the Grand Prix!
That was the best!
That was the dreamy-cutest!
All right!
Oh! Er...
The winner of the first Idol Time Grand Prix is Miss Yui!
Congratulations!
Yui, you were awesome!
Congrats!
That must be...
a new rare outfit.
Dream Rare?
And just who was that girl earlier?
That girl...
I wonder who she was.
I will have to investigate.
Meganii?
PriPara's super rad!
Crazy stuff!
Today was the Grand Prix, wasn't it?
Well, I couldn't care less.
Hm?
Isn't the winner your little sister?
Whoa, no freaking way! That's rad!
That's bull!
This GirlPara thing is messed up!
Yui!
Congratulations!
Congratulations-pri!
Thank you!
I'm so happy it's like I'm dreaming!
Puni!
All finished, warm and fresh!
Profiting to the max!
Nino, I'm all right, I swear.
Relax!
I can walk by myself.
Like I said, no going nuts on that ankle.
Gotta look after your pals, after all!
Okay, well, thank you.
Ah, my heart's still pounding!
The Grand Prix was amazing!
That was a real jerk move, though –
you didn't tell me it was a Grand Prix!
Wait, what? We didn't?
Oh, well, whatever.
"Fall seven times, get up eight"!
I'll just have to win the next Grand Prix!
Yumekawa! I saw your performance earlier.
Principal! Oh, um, well, you see...
Congratulations on winning the Grand Prix.
Huh?
I was able to observe your courage
closely from the audience in PriPara.
Indeed. And to be honest,
I was simply...
ba-blown away!
I had misunderstood PriPara this whole time.
PriPara is wonderful!
Viva PriPara! Baba PriPara!
So does that mean we can...
Most certainly it does! In fact, I'll be pushing you
to go to PriPara from now on!
All right!
Ye've not seen the last of me!
Perfect marks!
Next Episode
Hooray! I'm finally coming back to Parajuku!
So this is Parajuku?
This place is practically sacred!
It's like I'm in a dream!
And we're right into huge trouble!
What do you mean, we have to keep
performing or everything blows up?
A-Anyway, we have to keep the performances coming!
Here we go! Are you feeling it?
Wake up and smell the idols!
Capisce!
We'll show you the true power of us Parajuku idols!
Next time, Let's Go! Parajuku!
Let's Go! Parajuku
Come on, everyone! It's time to be an idol!