I'm Yumekawa Yui!
I've always dreamed of being a dreamy-cute super idol,
but even though there's a PriPara for boys
here in Paparajuku, BoyPara,
there isn't one for girls!
But they finally made one,
and I made my dreamy idol debut!
If you keep wishing, your dreams will come true!
And don't you dream to forget it!
Here we go! Are you feeling it?
Wake up and smell the idols!
Dreamy-cute!
Capisce!
And this is Manaka Lala.
She just transferred into Avocado Academy.
Dig Here, Idol
We're in primary school class 6-A together,
and she keeps insisting she's a Divine Idol in PriPara.
Would you come back to reality already?
I keep telling you, it's true!
Aw, sure it is.
And we're living in the same room at the dorm too!
Here's to a dreamyful friendship.
What the dream?
Wh-What's up?
Hey, there she is!
So mascots can go into the Idol Watch, huh?
That makes sense.
D-Does it?
I guess so.
I guess we can be together all the time. Right, Punicorn?
Puni...
All tidied up!
Man, I've always wanted to sleep in a bunk bed!
The way they join together's just like panini!
Panini?
It's an Italian sandwich.
I want to have one of Dad's panini right now!
Dad?
Hey, Lala. How come you came to Parajuku anyway?
Don't tell me...
The ship your mother and father were on sunk!
Your stepmother was wicked and cruel to you,
and cast you out!
How simply awful!
I mustn't ask. I mustn't make her remember!
We Divine Idols were sent to different towns
and we're supposed to raise hype for their PriParas.
Mirei and Sophie too.
Oh, Mirei and Sophie are my SoLaMi SMILE
teammates and fellow Divine Idols.
Uh, Yui?
Earth to Yui...
Wh-What an ordeal you've been through...
Oh, it's not that bad.
Being away from my folks is a little lonely, I'll admit.
No! Not your family!
But, hey, I get a discount
at the PriPara Café and stuff too.
Don't worry!
I'm sure you'll be able to dream happy in Paparajuku!
Um... c-capisce.
Dreamy-cute!
Cooking completed.
Praise be to Cooky, almighty rice cooker!
Mm, fresh rice and dreams, served steaming hot!
Ta-dah!
Yumeprika rice!
You're having rice as a side dish... for rice?
Yep! It's really good.
You wanna try some Yumeprika?
No... we're good for rice.
I still think getting people in Paparajuku
excited about girls' PriPara is impossible.
Yeah, there's no way a girl could be an idol.
Being an idol's totally a boy thing.
A boy thing?
Yes, a boys' PriPara:
BoyPara!
There's a BoyPara now?
You didn't have one in Parajuku?
They sure didn't.
What? Are you serious?
You really came from a weird backwards town.
Is it... really backwards?
Look, over there.
That's Shougo!
He's a member of WITH,
one of the hottest units in BoyPara!
He's so cute!
BoyPara all the way, am I right?
What's so cute about my dumb brother?
They wouldn't say that if they knew
what he was really like.
Hey, so anyway...
Yui, that girl we saw perform in PriPara earlier...
That was you, right?
Yep!
You watched it?
Shh!
You've got to keep quiet.
If the head disciplinarian catches wind of it,
Principal Babaria will...
All eyes on your principal, Ookandagawa Babaria.
It appears that a girls' PriPara
has opened close to the academy.
PriPara is an activity for boys.
A female idol is the epitome of unseemliness!
Our female students shall not forsake propriety!
Continue to lead a life of study and decorum!
Then the girls' PriPara which has
besmirched our neighbourhood
will soon wither and die.
What the dream?
What the heck?
Switching to warming mode.
Hey, dream the mood in here!
Dreamzzz... dreamzzz...
I think I'll have my work cut out for me
making PriPara popular in Parajuku...
But I won't give up!
Goodnight capisce!
Good morning!
Stare...
Be cool...
Good morning...
Next!
Here I come, yo!
Hup!
And land.
That was amazing!
Nah, it was nothing.
I reckon half marks.
Cheers!
That girl's incredible!
She's in class 6-C.
I wish I could be athletic like her...
Dream jump!
Go!
I'm flying!
Next.
Y-Yeah...
Ouchie-ouch...
That wasn't like I dreamed...
Amigo! Domingo! Let's go – ha!
But sorry, folks – the end's approa-chin'
and that's all for me today.
Babaria-bing-bong!
Yumekawa Yui of class 6-A,
come to the principal's office immediately!
Babaria-bong-bing.
PRINCIPAL'S OFFICE
Yumekawa!
I understand you performed in PriPara yesterday.
Wha– how do you know...
Nothing escapes my watchful eye.
It follows you everywhere you Ji-go-ku.
Walls have eyes and doors have ears.
I have beautiful and free reign over my domain.
But it's not like PriPara is officially banned.
And BoyPara's allowed, so...
Ulp.
Shut up, young lady!
Yumekawa Yui!
Your shameful inattention in class today was laid bare
before me, myself and eye.
I wasn't inattentive.
I was just daydreaming!
As punishment for attending PriPara,
you shall weed the school's entire rear grounds!
Do it after school every day.
You are forbidden from receiving any help.
Undreamable...
Until the very last weed is pulled.
No dreaming way!
Going to PriPara's become a distant dream again!
It'll take a fortnight to clear all these weeds!
Then I'll idol twice as hard for you!
I'll go around and get everyone excited for PriPara.
One, two! One, two! One, two! One, two!
Change formation!
Change!
One, two! One, two! One, two! One, two!
H-Hey there.
Won't you come to PriPara
with me and try being an idol?
Rui?
Gai?
Ai?
Chia?
Chii?
PriPara?
Won't you come to PriPara
with me and try being an idol?
PriPara?
No can do, got it?
What? But...
Our destination, you see...
That's right!
We're going to BoyPara, okay?
You're going to BoyPara?
Bravo boy's PriPara, BoyPara!
Today's another excursion.
B-But I though only boys were
allowed to dream into BoyPara...
Well, duh! And that's why...
Change formation!
Baa!
You're goats?
We're sheep. The Sheep Squad, got it?
Sheep?
Sheep and goats both go "baa"?
How are they different?
Goats say "baa", you see.
While sheep are more "baa".
Oh – I get it now! Capisce!
Baa.
Baa. Baa.
You dug a tunnel?
The Cheerleading Club is just a cover.
It's actually been a BoyPara fanclub its whole history.
Our predecessors worked themselves to the bone
digging this tunnel you see now.
They even made a miniature
Mount Fuji from the excavated earth.
Whoa!
It leads all the way into BoyPara.
Inside BoyPara?
Indeed. And that means even girls
can sneak into BoyPara as well!
And since we're dressed like this,
no one'll figure out we're really girls.
See? Our covers are p-perfect.
Okay, let's get going.
In formation!
Baa!
Baa.
Baa-baa!
Wait up!
I'm going to check this out.
Yui, you stay here and weed.
What?
Hup.
Baa-baa!
There's seriously a tunnel down here...
Um, so... if this way is that way, then this way must be...
And if I dig through here, then...
I can get to Prism Stone!
Tunnel
Mt. Fuji
Goal!!
Prism
Stone
Goal!!
Yeah, that ain't possible.
Capisce.
Hello? This is Minami Mirei, also known
as the Divine Idol Mirei from SoLaMi SMILE.
Head Disciplinarian Minami!
It's pretty smooth sailing over here, Lala.
Are you bringing excitement
to Paparajuku as calculated?
My calculations say it might not be going too well.
Huh? Oh! Um...
No, no, things are going great! Super smooth!
Really?
I – I'm a Divine Idol too, you know!
Man, it's too popular!
We've got a whole trillion guests – it's out of control!
The world population is only 7 billion.
A-Anyway, how about you?
You're at the Aquaprium PriPara, right?
Darn tootin'.
If you do find yourself in a tight spot, Manaka,
remember everything we went through
to become Divine Idols.
It'll be a cinch compared to that.
Nothing's impossible, you know.
Prez...
You're right. Nothing's impossible!
Capisce!
One, two, dream, four...
Dream...
Dream?
Shougo.
What on earth are you doing?
I'm dream-weeding.
Not that.
I happened to look at PriPara TV,
and I saw you performing.
You were watching me?
Who ever heard of a girl idol?
You trying to embarrass me?
Don't do something so lame ever again, got it?
Lame?
Weeding really suits you.
Oh yeah?
Well, wetting the bed suits you!
Shougo, Age 7
You win this round! Bleah!
Hey, it's Shougo!
When's your next show?
I wanna hear that song again!
Squee, squee, squee, squee!
The next show? Right now!
Whenever I'm around,
it's showtime!
Full Shougo ahead!
You two-faced phony!
I'll make that jerk dream his words!
Dreamy-cute!
Capisce!
Dream... Dream...
Dreamy-cute!
Capisce!
Baa-baa!
Those two are really going at it, aren't they?
It's been a whole week.
Capisce! Capisce!
Such admirable fortitude they have.
zzzdream... zzzdream...
The whole world shines before your eyes!
I'm all dreamed with weeding, so I'll help you out!
It's the home stretch!
Yui! And Suzu and Hana?
A certain someone dragged us here.
So now we're here, we may as well lend a hand.
Thank you very capisce!
We're all friends!
We're all friends, all friends!
We're all waiting for you
to come to PriPara!
Dreamy-cute!
Capisce!
Dreamy...
We must be getting close to PriPara now...
Yeah...
In formation!
It's the Sheep Squad!
Go! While we hold the roof!
Why? I don't capisce!
BoyPara and PriPara...
though we may walk different paths...
We hold the same feelings of love in our hearts!
We know it well, you see!
"Go ahead! We'll take care of it" –
don't think I'm saying that, okay?
Thank you!
One, two...
I think we...
will be good friends.
Did we dream through?
Up there!
That's a manhole lid!
Come on!
It won't open!
Dig deep...
One, two and...
Ahem.
Shiko
The sky above so lovely.
Shiko knows love, yet is so coy.
Dosu-coy.
Dosu-coy!
We did it!
Lala!
Yui!
We made it!
This is pretty awesome.
Hooray!
Welcome. Thank you for visiting Prism Stone.
Oh, I see you've brought some friends!
Suzu, Hana, this is your first time, right?
Then let's pick some outfits!
Please take your Idol Watches –
and also these PriTicket
Pretty Showbags we just got in today!
Thank you!
Jump!
PriPara Change!
Dreamy-cute!
Capisce!
Hana!
Suzu!
This way!
No way. This is crazy cute!
Whoa, is this really me?
This is my style, all right!
Your own biggest fan, huh?
You're both super dreamy-cute!
Heck yeah! You look great!
They suit you to a T!
Gee, thanks!
PriPara's really amazing!
Miss Lala dug the most out of everyone,
and it's maxed out her Idol Time!
You can now give a three-minute performance!
All right!
Woo-hoo!
Now I'll prove I'm a Divine Idol!
Really, that joke again?
Puni-puni!
Scan the appropriate number
of My Tickets for your outfit.
Countdown to Idol Time!
Unveiling SoLaMi SMILE's new team outfit,
a bustling affair studded all over
with cute and cool emblems!
Happy Emblem Cherry Ensemble!
Start!
Go for it, Miss Lala!
What?
That's Lala?
Wha-at?
Here's my idol form again!
With a "capisce"...
Lala's back, everyone!
It... wasn't a dream!
She really was the Divine Idol Lala
from SoLaMi SMILE...
She's really a dreamy Divine Idol!
Stop trying to be like that other girl
oshare na ano ko mane suru yori
You're already the number-one girl you can be
jibunrashisa ga ichiban desho
Can't you feel it in your heart?
haato no kagayaki kanjita nara
Let's go look for our own ideals
risou sagashi ni dekakeyou yo
And every single memory we make
fueteiku omoide zenbu
We'll snap in two and
pakin to hanbunko de
Complete the set with our friends
tomodachi konpuriito shiyou
Make it! You're unbeatable once you get started
make it doki doki suru toki muteki desho
Make up! Headed for a gloriously shining future
make up kira kira mirai de kimari desho
Your dreams aren't out of reach
yume wa mou yume ja nai
Making Drama, switch on!
Anyone can make theirs come true
dare datte kanaerareru
Lady! Ready to go – to paradise!
redi ready to go paradise
Twirling!
Exciting!
Deliver it to everyone!
Present for you!
Make it – I don't ever want to let go of this dream
make it akirametakunai yume dakara
Cyalume Time!
Make up – I don't want to give it up before I even start
make up akogare no mama ja iya dakara
Make it! You're unbeatable once you get started
make it doki doki suru toki muteki desho
Capisce!
Make up! You're headed for a gloriously shining future
make up kira kira mirai de kimari desho
Your dreams aren't out of reach
yume wa mou yume ja nai
Anyone can make theirs come true
dare datte kanaerareru
PriPara Pri-paradise
puripara puriparadaisu
That was amazing!
You were so cute, Lala!
Lala! You were undreamably incredible!
Everyone, PriPara is a place that all girls'
dreams are granted!
Come on to PriPara every day
and make your dreams come true!
I like it! You know I like it! Yui know I like it!
BoyPara is great, but girl idols are pretty great too!
We've gotta come to PriPara again!
A wonderful performance for Paparajuku's second ever!
And now – PriPara-ding-dong!
We have an announcement!
We will be holding a tournament this June!
A tournament?
A tournament...
I can get heaps of new fans! This chance is like a dream!
All right! I'll do my best!
To see Paparajuku's PriPara
grow into a splendid theme park,
please do your best and bring many new idols!
Okay! Let's go for it, Yui!
Yeah!
You got it, Lala! One, two...
Capisce!
Here we go!
Are you feeling it?
Wake up and smell the idols...
Dreamy-cute!
Next Episode
The tunnel's all done!
Now all the girls can link hands and head off to PriPara...
Hey! Quit dreaming out on me – come back to Earth!
We've still got a long way to go!
We've gotta keep on performing and spread the word about PriPara's amazingness!
Para Wrap
Okay! And I'll create a Making Drama jam-packed with dreamy-cute!
Hand in hand...
Come back to Earth!
Dreamy-Cute
NNotebook
Next time, Dreamy-Cute! Making Drama!
Dreamy-Cute!
Making Drama!
Come on, everyone! It's time to be an idol!