PriPara Café opens today!
It's like a dream come true!
And not just the café –
Paparajuku's PriPara's gonna be packed to the dreams!
Hi Lala! Are you doing well-pri?
Mirei!
I sure am!
And you too?
And PriPara? I doubt there are a trillion idols there,
but it's thriving to a reasonable de-pri?
Oh... yeah.
It's pretty smooth sailing over here, Lala.
Are you bringing excitement
to Paparajuku as calculated?
My calculations say it might not be going too well.
Huh? Oh! Um...
No, no, things are going great! Super smooth!
Really?
I – I'm a Divine Idol too, you know!
Man, it's too popular!
We've got a whole trillion guests – it's out of control!
The world population is only 7 billion.
Wow, I can hardly dream for all the fabulous cuisine!
Say what? There's an hour's wait if I wanna buy a crêpe?
They're in really high demand!
Yui? What are you fantasising about now?
Wow! Th-That's pri-ncredible!
And now the local Paparajuku specialty
PriParusk sold out? In 15 minutes?
Say it isn't so!
But what? There are more brand shops than in Parajuku?
What a dream!
There are that many?
I have to say, Lala, I'm pri-mpressed!
Living up to your title of Divine Idol-pri!
Um...
Er, well...
I'm even more psyched to come see you tomorrow-pri!
I'm between a dream and a hard place...
What? You're coming to see me?
Howdy.
The Osaka-pu PriPara's got a full house every day.
We've hit the visitor goal quicker than expected,
so my job's com-pri-te!
I can finally take a holiday and come see you-pri!
You can what?
Pri you tomorrow!
Capisce...
Yui, what do I do?
Mirei's coming here tomorrow!
M-Mirei is?
Mirei as in Lala's SoLaMi SMILE unitmate,
whose "pri-pri" sentence ender is known to all?
I've gotcha – pri!
It's like a dream!
Pri-pri!
Mi-re-i!
Boo-hoo...
Howpri-do?
It's Mirei, Y'all!
What am I gonna do?
Mirei's really coming here!
Is that bad?
Well, you see...
You what?
Why did you lie about that?
Well...
This PriPara's still
totally empty! No one visits and there are no buildings.
You should have just told her that.
Aren't you both SoLaMi SMILE unitmates?
Yeah! But, I mean,
Mirei and Sophie are working so hard
as proper Divine Idols at their own PriParas...
I'm sure they have their hands full already!
I couldn't make them worry about me too...
Now I dream where you're coming from.
Puni...
That's not all... Mirei's also really scary
when she gets all lecture-y and stuff.
She'd blow her top if she saw me now, I know it!
Synchronisation complete!
Huh? Wh-What?
Start it off low and then turn up the heat!
Don't let Dad lift the lid till it's ready to eat!
Lala, is something the matter?
Wow, Cooky's talking now!
And his tone sounds different from before!
So dreamy-cute!
You can boil away all your worries
with Hologrammation!
Hey, yeah!
Let's go and try it!
Hologrammation, you say?
Unfortunately, we can't let you use it!
What?
There are only a few users in PriPara at the moment,
so we're in power-conserving mode.
And Hologrammation is a huge energy drain.
Can't you make an exception?
We don't need the whole thing, just one spot.
What if I use this Divine Idol Coupon?
Valid throughout
Divine Idolhood
Divine
Idol Coupon
Valid throughout
Divine Idolhood
Divine
Idol Coupon
Valid throughout
Divine Idolhood
Divine
Idol Coupon
Valid throughout
Divine Idolhood
Divine
Idol Coupon
Valid throughout
Divine Idolhood
Divine
Idol Coupon
Valid throughout
Divine Idolhood
Divine
Idol Coupon
Valid throughout
Divine Idolhood
Divine
Idol Coupon
Valid throughout
Divine Idolhood
Divine
Idol Coupon
Valid throughout
Divine Idolhood
Divine
Idol Coupon
Valid throughout
Divine Idolhood
Divine
Idol Coupon
Valid throughout
Divine Idolhood
Divine
Idol Coupon
Valid throughout
Divine Idolhood
Divine
Idol Coupon
Valid throughout
Divine Idolhood
Divine
Idol Coupon
Valid throughout
Divine Idolhood
Divine
Idol Coupon
Valid throughout
Divine Idolhood
Divine
Idol Coupon
Valid throughout
Divine Idolhood
Divine
Idol Coupon
Valid throughout
Divine Idolhood
Divine
Idol Coupon
Valid throughout
Divine Idolhood
Divine
Idol Coupon
Valid throughout
Divine Idolhood
Divine
Idol Coupon
Very well.
Just the one Hologrammation device.
Thank you so much!
Puni!
And all set.
Beep-boop.
Wow! Amazing!
Hey, I just dreamed up a great idea!
Let's borrow mannequins from Prism Stone.
Anyone hungerin' for some luncheon?
Right here, ma'am – I'll take an okonomiyaki rice 'un!
Thanking you kindly.
Okonomiyaki & Rice
Lunch Set
The Good Ol' Classic Taste!
Okonomiyaki & Rice
Lunch Set
The Good Ol' Classic Taste!
Okonomiyaki & Rice
Lunch Set
The Good Ol' Classic Taste!
Okonomiyaki & Rice
Lunch Set
The Good Ol' Classic Taste!
Okonomiyaki & Rice
Lunch Set
The Good Ol' Classic Taste!
Okonomiyaki & Rice
Lunch Set
The Good Ol' Classic Taste!
Okonomiyaki & Rice
Lunch Set
The Good Ol' Classic Taste!
Okonomiyaki & Rice
Lunch Set
The Good Ol' Classic Taste!
Okonomiyaki & Rice
Lunch Set
The Good Ol' Classic Taste!
Okonomiyaki & Rice
Lunch Set
The Good Ol' Classic Taste!
Okonomiyaki & Rice
Lunch Set
The Good Ol' Classic Taste!
Okonomiyaki & Rice
Lunch Set
The Good Ol' Classic Taste!
Okonomiyaki & Rice
The mannequins are working like a dream!
And now...
Ta-da!
Some more props I made out of cardboard!
See? Doesn't this place look packed now?
Way to go!
The cover's perfect! She'll be totally fooled!
Was I right or was I right?
It might really look like there's a whole trillion!
But there's something just not quite right.
Hm, it might be too quiet.
Leave it to me! I'll fix that rice away!
Cooky?
I'll cook up some lively sound effects
for you – on the house!
That's incredible! Now it's a total party!
That's my Cooky!
This'll do it, Lala! We've got this in the bag!
There's no way Mirei will think it's fake.
Thank goodness! And thank you!
Welcome
Mirei
I might have got here too early.
I hope they have enough time to set up too.
Are you Yui?
I'm sorry?
Wow, she looks so plain.
Maybe she's a fan of mine!
I can get her interested in PriPara!
Is this your first time here?
Yes, it is.
Welcome to PriPara, my dear!
And don't worry. Even serious, frumpy, unpopular girls
can become shining idols
when they step through the gate!
That's the wonder of PriPara!
Do you like PriPara?
I... love it...
Then you'll be fine!
I expect as much, yes.
There's still time before we're supposed to meet.
You must feel anxious by yourself.
Allow me to escort you.
I'd love that.
Jump!
PriPara Change!
Dreamy-cute!
Pri-pri!
Thanks for being my escort, Yui!
Mi-Mi-Mi – you were Mirei?
Wah – you look crazy different!
What do I do now? Ah, I'm such a dumb idiot!
I've been so rude to Mirei the Divine Idol!
I don't think I can ever dream this down!
A pri-ntriguing girl. I think I like her.
I was such a dreaming idiot...
Hey, Mirei! You and Yui are already friends!
I know that voice – Lala!
Long time no pr–i?
Huh?
Lala?! Why are you still all short-pri?
Uh...
Wha-at?
You scanned a damaged PriTicket and
glitched out the system, and this is the pri-sult...
is what you're saying-pri?
That's pri-diculous.
So this is Paparajuku's PriPara, is it?
While there's certainly not a trillion idols,
it does seem pri-nvigorated.
No need to look too closely...
Why would that pri?
Puni-puni!
Wow, what a little cutie-pri!
Nice timing, Punicorn!
This is Punicorn, my manager!
Pri-eased to meet you.
Punicorn.
That's the stuff-pri! A new manager, and a new PriPara:
everything here's so prilliant and pristine I'm en-pri-ous!
So anyway, there's this place that makes
yummy flan in front of Paparajuku station!
We should call it a day for PriPara and go grab some!
No, no, I want to see more of
this new PriPara! Show me around!
I want to see the fruits of my dear friend
Lala the Divine Idol's work-pri!
I want to pri-eally take in all the details!
O-Okay.
You've done a pri fantastic job here, I must say!
Man, I just can't lie to Mirei.
I have to tell her the truth and apologise.
Pri-pri-pri!
Um, actually, M-Mirei,
there's something I have to tell you...
Wow! Paparajuku's PriPara is pri-ncredible, I'll admit!
Ah!
Pri!
You wouldn't find such solidly-built girls
anywhere else, that's for sure-pri!
All thanks to you, hiding in there, I pri-sume!
Ripe white rice-wheat reapers rue and regret.
Beep-boop.
What on earth is going on here?
This place is com-pri-tely deserted!
We're sorry!
I'm pri-nfuriated, you know, Lala!
I don't blame you for being mad.
I'm supposed to be a Divine Idol, but I'm useless!
That's not what I'm mad about-pri!
Mirei?
That's a friendship inpringement!
Talk your dear friend Mirei first
if you're worried about something-pri!
Oh, Mirei!
Now, there's nothing else
you're keeping to yourself, is there-pri?
Or you, Yui?
Um, about that...
What, there is-pri?
Actually...
They announced they'd be holding
this Idol Time Grand Prix in Paparajuku, but...
If we don't get enough participants
and can't hold the event,
Paparajuku's PriPara will be closed.
And Miss Lala will be fired from being a Divine Idol!
Idol Time Grand Prix
You're kidding!
But I'm not going to let the Grand Prix end in failure!
That's some pri-ncredible confidence you have there,
considering the situation.
That clinches it-pri.
I suppose the great Mirei, saviour of the Osaka-pu PriPara,
will have to lend you a hel-pri-ng hand!
All right! Thanks, Mirei, we love you!
Puni!
And that's why...
I, the Divine Idol Minami Mirei,
have come to the Avocado Academy girls' dorms
to give a talk on PriPara's charm!
PriPara, huh?
I don't really see the appeal.
Please see the following.
And flip!
Making Friends
89%
Becoming More Outgoing
92%
Having Fun Every Day
96%
Not Feeling Lonely
Even Without a Boyfriend
77%
Making Friends
89%
Becoming More Outgoing
92%
Having Fun Every Day
96%
Not Feeling Lonely
Even Without a Boyfriend
77%
Making Friends
89%
Becoming More Outgoing
92%
Having Fun Every Day
96%
Not Feeling Lonely
Even Without a Boyfriend
77%
Making Friends
89%
Becoming More Outgoing
92%
Having Fun Every Day
96%
Not Feeling Lonely
Even Without a Boyfriend
77%
Making Friends
89%
Becoming More Outgoing
92%
Having Fun Every Day
96%
Not Feeling Lonely
Even Without a Boyfriend
77%
Making Friends
89%
Becoming More Outgoing
92%
Having Fun Every Day
96%
Not Feeling Lonely
Even W i t h out a Boyfriend
77%
Making friends,
becoming more outgoing,
having fun every day.
According to our research,
going to PriPara has this and other advantages.
Furthermore, in PriPara, everyone's an idol.
Making Friends
89%
Becoming More Outgoing
92%
Having Fun Every Day
96%
Not Feeling Lonely
Even Without a Boyfriend
77%
92%
89%
As a matter of fact, even I...
Making Friends
89%
Becoming More Outgoing
92%
Having Fun Every Day
96%
Not Feeling Lonely
Even Without a Boyfriend
77%
Making Friends
89%
Becoming More Outgoing
92%
Having Fun Every Day
96%
Not Feeling Lonely
Even Without a Boyfriend
77%
Making Friends
89%
Becoming More Outgoing
92%
Having Fun Every Day
96%
Not Feeling Lonely
Even Without a Boyfriend
77%
transform greatly when I set foot in PriPara.
That's right, a sparkling idol-pri!
You should all try it as well.
Yes, you. And you as well.
You'll meet a brand-new you, I'm sure of it!
No matter where you Ji-go-ku...
the walls and the doors both have ears.
Head Disciplinarian Jigoku Mimiko
lies unnoticed, hearing and knowing all.
The fearsome Head Disciplinarian appears!
So you're the Head Disciplinarian of Avocado Academy.
May I, Minami Mirei, Head Disciplinarian
of Paprika Academy, be of some service?
Article 171 of the Avocado Academy school regulations:
No invading the quarters of another school's dormitories!
Article 874: No giving lectures without authorisation!
Article 5,151: No corrupting students
by luring them towards the evil of PriPara!
As Head Disciplinarian,
I shall not sanction such transgressions!
Very interesting.
Let me show the old-school grit I polished in Osaka.
And incidentally, Jigoku.
I assume you're familiar with Avocado Academy
school regulations article 373?
Three hundred, three hundred...
Article 373:
Students must behave amicably
towards those from other schools.
In other words, the attitude you have adopted
against me is a breach of school regulations.
Unfortunately for you,
I must advise you that exceptions are allowed
when our students are threatened by said outsiders.
We're not really in any danger, though.
Yeah.
I am taking preliminary action
to prevent such peril from coming about.
W-Well, no one asked you to.
Yeah.
I have all your best interests at heart!
You're a disgrace to the title of Head Disciplinarian.
Say again?
If you're as sharp-eared as say, you'll be well aware
of the Exemplary Head Disciplinarian Contest, won't you?
National
Exemplary Head Disciplinarian Contest
But of course...
The title it confers is aspired to
by all elite head disciplin...
You couldn't be...
None other.
Now allow me, Minami Mirei,
three-year consecutive champion and
hall of fame entrant, to teach you a little something.
This is how you deliver a ticket to miscreant.
What impeccable form.
If this loss stings, then practise
a thousand times in front of a mirror.
I – I'll remember this day!
That takes care of that thorn in our side.
Any of you interested in PriPara,
let's go there together!
Okay!
This is a secret underground passage leading to PriPara.
If we take this route, we can go to PriPara undetected
even if the disciplinary committee blocks the path.
Do you reckon PriPara has rollercoasters and stuff?
Maybe. I don't really know what it's like.
They don't seem familiar
with Paparajuku's PriPara at all.
They couldn't dream up any interest, I guess.
But if it got broadcast on TV and stuff more,
I bet more people would be interested in it.
Then why don't you try spreading the word yourselves?
But how?
Come on, people go on sites like PriTube
and Pri Pri Douga a lot these days.
If you stream it online, people in other cities can see
and you don't have the hassle of large-scale equipment.
I bet Meganee would gladly help you out.
I never dreamed of that!
Great idea, Prez!
You've got to reach out to
Paparajuku's girls more proactively!
Hup!
So this is the place.
Everyone!
Do you all have your MyTickets?
And did you pick up your Idol Watches
and Pretty Showbags?
Yep!
Wow! This looks so cute!
So do you, Ricchan!
I hardly recognise you all-pri!
Mirei!
It's just like you said, Mirei – I met a brand-new me!
Thank you!
Your Idol Time has been maxed out.
You can now give a three-minute performance!
Mirei! I want to see you put on a concert!
I dream of it too!
I want to see it!
Well, if you pri-nsist.
What do you say, Lala? Like old times-pri?
Capisce!
Wow! I've got to get Meganee
to set up a livestream for this!
Scan the appropriate number
of My Tickets for your outfit.
You can also scan each other's Friend Tickets.
Countdown to Idol Time!
Pri!
Outfits fit for Divine Idols –
decked out in an array of coloured-stripes,
they're fashioned with great skill!
Happy Emblem Cherry Ensemble!
Capisce!
And Miss Mirei is resplendent in blue!
The assortment of pin badges give it a funky feeling!
Happy Emblem Aqua Ensemble!
Start-pri!
Start!
Dreams times effort
yume ni kakeru zenryoku
Friendship times friendship
yuujou kakeru yuujou
Mix it up, roll the marbles
mazemaze maaburu
Blast right on past paradise
yukou paradaisu koete
We don't even know the rules
shiritai asobishigusa
No, you won't believe your eyes
nido misuru you na kiseki
Who could divine this mismatched duo?
kamiawanai futari wa
We've got a dream of Divine Idolhood
kami aidoru wo mezasu no
Steppin' out of time, ahead of the beat
biito otte oshinuke
Not just a touch, but not all dolled up
nachu demo nekome demo nai
Got that sweet dreamy flair and the NON STYLE look
non sutairu no yumegao
That's what us girls are gonna rock
otome natte miyou yo
Smiles for our eyeshadow
egao mabuta ni nose
With a pop!
popon
Come on, let's restyle ourselves
atarashii watashi e
It's makeup time!
let's make up
Making Drama, switch on!
Dreams times effort
yume ni kakeru zenryoku
Our voices times standing our ground
koe wo kakeru nigasanai
I'm lousy with maths
suuji ja wakannai
Yay!
So just break past our hearts' parameters
mune no parameetaa kowase
You can give in to curiosity (It's okay)
koukishin ni nara makete (ii yo)
But don't ever give in to regrets!
demo ne koukai ni makecha dame da
Fresh Sweets Park!
Never ever!
dame da
Cyalume Time!
Dreams times effort
yume ni kakeru zenryoku
Friendship times friendship
yuujou kakeru yuujou
Spread it all around the world
tsukutte hirogeru
Capisce!
Pri-pri-pri!
It's the Marble Paradise, a-ha-ha!
maaburu paradaisu ahaha
Wow-ee! I've never seen such amazing outfits before!
Marble
maaburu
A-ha-ha!
ahaha
Mirei!
Miss Mirei and Miss Lala have been awarded
some Super Cyalume Ensembles!
I wasn't expecting to get such a rare outfit
here in Paparajuku! Pri cool!
I lost myself in the moment there, but I guess we did it!
Divine Idols really are dreamazing!
That was the best performance ever!
This idol Mirei's the Minami
who came to visit today, isn't she?
She's like a different person!
I might try going to PriPara too!
We'll come again!
See you then!
Bye bye-pri!
Come again if you're free and you'll have a bowl!
Hello, this is Mirei-pri.
What's that? I'm being dispatched to Iparaki?
Pri-ead you loud and clear!
I'll be there before you can say "pri"!
What? You're going again already, Mirei?
A Divine Idol's work is never done-pri.
Lala, next time you're in trouble,
I want you to tell me first-pri.
Capisce!
Oh, and Yui.
I'm all yu-ears!
Keep an eye on Lala for me, will you-pri?
Sure thing!
Make sure you give it a hundred pri-cent, you two!
Mm, warm and fresh!
National Exemplary Head Disciplinarian hall of fame...
Minami Mirei, to think you would go so far
as to learn Avocado Academy's regulations by heart...
Though it stings, yet I acknowledge you.
However!
This Mirei persona is unconscionable!
PriPara...
No, it cannae not be countenanced!
Next Episode
Hello! It's been a long time-kuma!
Ol' me here, the ultra super Divine manager,
has dropped into Paparajuku's PriPara-kuma!
Punicorn?
So you're the newbie manager-kuma?
Well, listen up – the test of a manager's mettle
is making their idol shine-kuma!
And that's ol' me's gonna
train you up right smart-kuma!
Puni?
Don't you get a big head 'cause you're a little cute-kuma!
We're gonna whip you into shape, no holds beared!
Next time, Manager Training for Punicorn-kuma!
Manager Training
for Punicorn-kuma!
Come on, everyone! It's time to be an idol!