How wonderful!
We dreamed our best and dug out this whole tunnel!
And now all these girls are headed to PriPara.
Yui! Yui!
Come back to us, Yui!
Hey, come on! Come back, Yui!
I guess my dream's still a distant dream...
But we dug the tunnel out perfectly!
Safety first, you know.
I guess you're right!
I want to dreamy-cutify this tunnel to PriPara even more
and fill it to the dreams with dreamy-cute idols!
Capisce to that!
Let's do it!
Okay! It'll be a dream!
I'm Yumekawa Yui.
For a long time, we only had
a boys' PriPara here in Paparajuku,
but a girls' PriPara finally sprung into dreaming.
And I made my long-dreamed idol debut!
We'll go, we'll feel it, we'll wake up
and smell the idols today too!
Full of happiness and full of dreams!
Dreamy-Cute!
Making Drama!
Cooking completed.
Cooked to perfection as always!
Para Wrap
Here you go, Lala. Thanks for your hard work on the tunnel!
Thanks!
Yui, your rice balls are so fluffy and warm!
Here, Hana, Suzu. You have some too.
Th-Thank you.
But, uh, we're...
...kinda eating toast here. In case you couldn't tell.
Rice dreams along together with everyone.
Whether it's bread, okonomiyaki or even ramen,
rice believes in peace between everyone!
Now eat it all up!
Th-Thank you very much...
Puni.
Sorry for the wait, Punicorn. You, have some too.
I've gotta eat up and dream my best
so I can perform again!
And get ready for that PriPara tournament in June!
Then first you've gotta create your own Making Drama.
That's what gives any idol a real logbook!
You mean "leg up"!
Leg up
A Making Drama!
That's it! You use them in your show
to convey your feelings to everyone.
For your first performance,
you used a premade Making Drama, right?
Dream you loud and clear! I need a Making Drama!
Shh, you two!
You shouldn't talk about that stuff here.
But the Disciplinary Committee isn't around at all.
You don't know anything, do you?
The Head Disciplinarian Jigoku Mimiko's ears
pick up anything you don't want heard.
She can hear a pin drop from over
a kilometre away, the rumours say.
A... whole kilometre?
No matter where you Ji-go-ku...
the walls and the doors both have ears.
Jigoku Mimiko stands before you.
I caught wind of a little rumour, you know.
That the two of you went to PriPara.
Eh? Wh-What a...
...funny rumour.
Furthermore, I believe I heard the word "PriPara"
loud and clear, spoken in the vicinity.
No?
Oh, well, that was...
Th-That's right! It wasn't "PriPara"...
I was talking about bream bara-sushi!
You combine the rice with sliced bream
and high-grade Chateaubriand steak.
Brighten it brilliantly with an Apita-made fine-bristled brush
that's a Cambrian hybrid, bream bara-sushi!
Done like a dream!
I can hear the sushi's voice.
The bream resents its treatment by the bristles...
Escape, escape, escape...
Man, that was a close one!
Hey, so you two are totally being marked.
Yeah, and this "girls being idols" thing just doesn't work.
Did you see yesterday's BoyPara show?
You bet I did! WITH was so incredible!
That's not true. I mean...
You've got a real, breathing female Divine Idol right here!
Huh, don'tcha?
I mean, I guess your concert earlier was okay...
"Okay"?
But crossing the principal's path?
Don't worry about a thing!
Once they see the super dreamy-cute
Making Drama I've been working on since I was a kid,
I'm sure they'll get the urge to go again!
I call it Yumekawa Yui the Dream-Dreaming
Dreamy-Cute Princess!
Oh, what a simply dreamy-cute fairytale forest!
All behold the idol beloved by all,
the dreamy-cute princess!
I'm the Dreamy-Cute Princess, Yumekawa Yui!
Time to dreamy-cutify you all!
Gather round, little ones!
May dreams fill your heart!
Here we go!
Dreamy-cute, dreaming heart: Yumekawa Yui!
Bear?
Tanu?
Boing?
Squeak!
Bleat!
Tweet!
My word!
And so once again, the dreamy-cute fairytale forest
grew ever more dreamy-cute, dreaming heart and lovely.
Hey, by the way, we've got
social studies first period, right?
Sure do!
Hey! No, wait!
The three great industrial regions are
the Keipin, Chuupyou and Hanpin areas.
What should I do for my Making Drama?
It's gotta be super dreamy-cute...
Hanpin Industrial
Region
Keipin Industrial
Now, who can tell me the greatest
industrial region in Japan today?
Yumekawa?
The most dreamy-cute industrial region...
Hey, Yumekawa?
The representative from Parajuku, Yumekawa Yui,
is this year's Miss Dreamy-Cute Industrial Region!
Thank you for electing me, everyone!
I'll work hard to be the best
Miss Dreamy-Cute Industrial Region around!
Whoever heard of Paparajuku anyway?
Kei-
pin
Who d'ya think you are, stealing Keipin's spotlight?
Han-
pin
You're a thorn in all our sides,
Keipin "Industrial land shortage" region!
Han-
pin
Y'all know this here Hanpin,
bigger 'n anyone and dating back
Han-
pin
to the Edo Period, 's the real number one around these parts!
Huh?
Well, then, our entrants,
shall we reopen the contest
and compete with Making Dramas?
Suits me fine, Missy!
Suits me fine!
Han-
pin
Kei-
Han-
pin
Kei-
Han-
pin
Kei-
Han-
pin
Kei-
Han-
pin
Kei-
Han-
pin
Kei-
Han-
pin
Kei-
Han-
pin
Kei-
Han-
pin
Kei-
Han-
pin
Kei-
Han-
pin
Kei-
Han-
pin
Kei-
Han-
pin
Kei-
Han-
pin
Oh no, what should I go about the Making Drama?
It's nowhere near finished!
Yumekawa!
Sit up and pay attention in class.
The correct answer was the Chuupyou Industrial Region.
Dreamy-cute!
Dreamy-cute... dreamy-cute!
This red carpet leads to a dreamy-cute castle!
For I am Cinderella, trapped in dreams!
Cindreamella's prince awaits her!
Good prince, prince of my dreams!
Um... Yui?
Here's some divine advice from Lala the Divine Idol –
when you can't figure something out, ask other people!
All right, let's scope out some ideas about dreamy-cute!
Not having much luck, are we?
Puni! Puni-puni-puni-puni, puni!
Hey, let's ask Punicorn too.
Punicorn, what makes dreamy-cute for you?
Punicorn! Punicorn. Punicorn.
Mm.
Punicorn!
Mm, yes.
Wow, Yui!
You can understand what she's saying?
Not a word!
You two.
Principal Babaria.
You've not ventured back
to that babarred PriPara, have you?
Oh – no! Definitely not!
Because you know if you set a single foot in there...
You'll be weeding not just
the school grounds but all of Paparajuku!
Yes, we fully understand!
BoyPara, hey! BoyPara, hey!
Parasite, plump and squishy,
li'l larva, ya love my plump ol' booty!
Plump and squishy!
Babario! Please refrain from shaking your hips
in such a baba-boorish way!
Aw, don't be such a stick-in-the mud, sis!
So no luck with the Making Drama?
Give it a try!
Nope...
Shake your booty, plump and squishy!
Sorry for dragging you along.
Don't be silly.
A friend in need's a friend indeed!
A friend...
Thanks, Lala! I'm gonna dream my best!
And first up...
Cooking completed.
Wow, chicken rice!
Yep! Can't think up Making Dramas on an empty stomach!
Let's eat!
Dreamy-Cute
NNotebook
Hey, I saw that notebook before...
Dreamy-Cute
Notebook
It's my dreamy-cute design notebook!
And I've got a few more.
This... is quite a few.
I've been sketching them since I was three.
Three?
You must really love dreamy-cute fashion, huh?
I sure do! More than dreams themselves!
But there's so much dreamy-cute I have in mind
that I don't know what to do with it...
Oh... well, um...
A Making Drama is a message for all and sundry.
Firstly, you have to think of what
you as an idol want to tell them.
A Making Drama is a message for all and sundry.
Firstly, you have to think of
what you as an idol want to tell them.
"What you as an idol want to tell them"?
That's it! For me, PriPara is
the most fun place in the world!
Just by passing through the gates,
you get filled with excitement and wonder!
Your dreams are within reach.
Even if you're shy, you can hold your head up high.
Any girl can be a shining idol!
So...
Lala!
That totally clicked with me just now.
You really are a Divine Idol!
Really? You mean it?
Puni, Punicorn!
I want everyone to understand too!
I want to show them how
dreamy-cute girl idols really are!
And fill PriPara with shining idols!
That's what I want to tell everyone!
Okay!
Puni!
Prepare for Head Disciplinarian
Jigoku Mimiko's inspection!
Inspection?
The Disciplinary Committee comes around
every night just before lights out at nine.
Really?
This sound...
Someone is concealing preserved goods.
Charge!
No! My grandmother sent me those
from all the way from the country!
Please overlook this!
Eating after eight o'clock
is an infringement upon the rules.
To Hell's crucible with it.
In it goes!
No!
This sound... is not single-ply but double!
Charge!
But it simply has to be double-ply!
Please, won't you overlook this?
Eco-friendliness above all!
For toilet paper, single is supreme!
To Hell's crucible with it.
In it goes!
No...
Wowsers! She really is super strict!
She's a law all by herself.
You wouldn't want to cross her.
We're denied both dreams and freedom.
No way...
Baa...
There's no way we can focus
on creating a Making Drama.
It's complete!
Yui?
I dreamed I completed my Making Drama.
But now I'm awake I don't remember a thing.
I'm kind of hungry. But...
If I tried to eat something,
I think it'd just be confiscated.
Then we'll go outside.
I know a way to cook a midnight snack.
Sneaky... sneaky...
You there!
Kidnapping is a crime, you know!
And you've bababducted my heart!
Oh, WITH! Shougo!
You make my heart go babub-dub! Mwah!
Cooking completed.
Sneaky-sneaky-sneaky-sneaky...
Who is it? Who is out this late?
Baba-ree-woo!
The heck's that, yo?
Can't let my late-night running get found out!
Baba-ree-woo! Baba-ree-woo! Baba-baba-ree!
Ow-ow-ow...
C'mon, this way!
Baba-ree-woo! Baba-ree! Baba-ree! Baba-ree!
They're not here!
Not here either!
That "baba" siren is an earsore!
Baba?
Hey, we're here...
No one'll find us here.
Here ya go.
Thanks a dream!
Thanks a lot!
Wait! At least tell us your name!
Heh, this here Nino's name ain't worth remembering.
But... you just told us.
So she's Nino.
Neither hide nor hair of them.
We'll call it off for tonight.
Understood.
Disciplinary Committee, you are dismissed.
Aye!
I do swear, on my all-hearing ears,
I shall seize your little tails.
It sure is condreamient
that we can use the tunnel to hide.
Yep, and these sheep costumes help us keep warm too.
Cooky can make ramen too, you know.
Now you pour the boiled water into Cooky,
and set the timer.
Amazing!
I think it's got even colder.
Look what I found!
Hey, Lala, do you remember
what I said this morning, cuckoo?
How I said I having dreamloads of girls
coming through this tunnel to PriPara was my dream...
cuckoo.
Cuckoo.
But I'm not going to let that stay a dream, cuckoo!
My dream's going to come true one day, I know it, coo!
So there's no way I'm giving up, cuckoo!
Darn right! Capisce, cuckoo!
I'm feeling sleepy, cuckoo...
But I never finished the Making Drama...
Yui, wake up, cuckoo! Wake up, cuckoo!
Cuckoo! Come on, come on!
Yui! Yui!
Cuckoo! Cuckoo!
A cuckoo clock, cuckoo...?
Three minutes has passed.
Three minutes...
When I become an idol,
I only get three minutes of Idol Time!
The ramen's ready! Come on, let's eat!
Three minutes...
A cuckoo clock...
A crescent moon...
Lala! It's complete, cuckoo!
My dreamy-cute Making Drama's all done!
Your Idol Time has been maxed out.
You can now give a three-minute performance!
All right!
I got a jewel!
I brought the others, Yui!
Wow, you all came to see me!
Yeah, but we were pretty much dragged here.
Come on, last time was a capisceload of fun, right?
And you'll have a dreamload this time too!
I can dream it clear as day!
Punicorn!
Scan the appropriate number
of My Tickets for your outfit.
Countdown to Idol Time!
Miss Yui says the concept for this outfit
is a dreamy-cute magical idol!
The wand chest accessory
seems bursting with spells to cast!
Magical Star Pink Ensemble!
Start!
Tick-tock magicalun-lun - Idol Time starts now!
chikutaku magica runrun aidoru taimu sutaato
Come on!
kamon
Everyone can be an idol!
Everyone has their time to shine dreamy-cute!
(Magical! Idol! Here we go!)
(majikaru aidoru here we go)
It's the magic girls long for
onna no ko ga akogaretekita mahou
A splendorous world where mysteries abound
fushigi wa joushiki chouisekai
I cast my spell and it's showtime
tonaetara shoutaimu
All I need is a little transformation and I'm ready
henshin shitara junbi bacchiri da yo
I feel like Cinderella
marude kibun wa shinderera
Beckoned secretly to the ball
kossori goshoutai
I'd better hurry up, cause everyone's waiting - no, no more limits
sore ja isogou minna matteru kitto anrimiteddo
Now the future is boundless
saa mirai eigou
Mark this moment in time!
toki o kizamu yo
(Tick-tock magical go!)
(chikutaku magikaru go)
Now hold on just a moment? I can't stop! Here, with my mic in hand
chotto jasutamoomen tomaranai yo maiku katate ni
Taking the hour hand and dancing, my heart singing
tanshin to dancing kokoro singing
In a thrilling singularity
tokimeki shingyuraritii
The mystery of the unclear is so entrancing
katachi no nai mono koso itsudatte hoshii yo
Music holds my hopes, so pretty and sweet
kibou to myuujikku puriti kyuuti
When I'm so excited I can't hold still
dokidoki machikirenai nara
Tick-tock magicalun-lun - it's Idol Time, and we're not done!
chikutaku magica runrun aidoru taimu tsuzuku yo
Is it a dream or reflection, truth or illusion? Who can say?
yume ka utsusu ka uso ka hontou ka dare mo wakaranai
Making Drama, switch on!
Adrift in the ebb and flow of time and space
watashi dake jikan fuuyuu kuukan
Until eternal twilight blooms
towairaito ga terasu made
Like a dream, dreamy-cute!
Tick-tock super Idol Time!
chikutaku super idol time
Tick and tock and
chii-ku ta-ku
Now just a moment, I hold my secrets always in my heart
jasutamoomen zutto zutto himitsu o mune ni
Whee!
It's dreamcredible: welcome to dreamland!
In the loveliest outfit, in a single breath
saikou no koode wanburesu de
Awakened by dream energy
mezameru doriimu enajii
Dreamy-cute Magical Clock Land!
The mystery of the unclear is so entrancing
katachi no nai mono koso itsudatte hoshii yo
Music holds my hopes, so pretty and sweet
kibou to myuujikku puriti kyuuti
Cyalume Time!
When I'm so excited I can't hold still
dokidoki machikirenai nara
Tick tock, I've gotta take it
chikutaku ima toraete
That chance comes just the once!
chansu wa isshun dake yo
Tick-tock magicalun-lun, now Idol Time: da capo!
chikutaku magica runrun aidoru taimu da kaapo
Miss Yui!
What a lovely performance!
You did amazing, Yui!
Totally!
Thanks a dream!
You were shining!
Girl idols really are great!
See, aren't you glad you came?
Yeah!
Hm? What is it?
What?
The PriPara Café is now open for business!
What? This... isn't a dream, is it?
No dreams here.
This is how PriPara gets made, building by building!
Okay! That means PriPara's just getting started!
I've gotta keep dreaming my best!
Capisce!
Now, let's keep the enthusiasm rolling.
We'll now announce the name of the tournament in June.
Idol Time Grand Prix
And it is...
The Idol Time Grand Prix!
And it's in June!
However...
If we don't get enough participants
and can't hold the event,
Paparajuku's PriPara will be closed.
What?
And Miss Lala will be fired from being a Divine Idol!
It's the system!
Idol Time Grand Prix
Wha-at?!
Next Episode
Hello! Former Divine Idol Lala here!
You can't give up, Lala!
We'll dream your best to make
the tournament a success!
Capisce! I'm bring heaps of girls to PriPara, just wait and see!
Howpri-do, Lala? It's been a pri long time!
Mirei?
Is Paparajuku nice and pri-nvigorated?
I can't wait to come around and shoot the pri-eeze!
Oh man, what do I do?
I've gotta hurry up and get some girls together!
Next time, Howpri-do? It's Mirei, Y'all!
Howpri-do?
It's Mirei, Y'all!
Come on, everyone! It's time to be an idol!