The Idol Time Grand Prix is underway at last!
Yui here!
I traversed many harsh dreams to make it here today.
But dreaming my bum off with Lala
was worth every dream!
Dreamy-cute! Dreamy-cute!
Thank you all for your dreamy-cute support!
Pu?
Puni?
Dreamy-cute! Dreamy-cute!
Yui! For crying out loud, Yui!
Punicorn!
Huh?
Where'd the crowd go?
There were about a million of them just now.
Puni.
I think you were daydreaming again.
More girls are coming to PriPara now,
but no one's becoming an idol.
We won't be able to hold the Grand Prix at this rate.
And I'll be fired from being a Divine Idol!
If that happens, does it mean we'll be torn apart too?
Yui! We're parting all too soon,
but thank you for being my friend!
Take this salmon rice ball as a parting gift!
I packed it full of all my feelings for you!
I couldn't bear that!
I'd prefer tuna and mayo to salmon, if you can!
Punicorn.
Puni, puni.
You're right, Punicorn.
There's no use feeling sorry for ourselves.
We need to get a dreamload more idols in here!
Capisce!
I Opened
a Fashion Studio, Got It?
My right shoulder... so heavy...
It feels as if something is weighing down on it.
I can't do this. No way, no way, no way...
Won't you be an idol?
Get together!
And be an
Idol!
Get together!
And be an
Idol!
Get together!
And be an
Idol!
Get together!
And be an
Idol!
Get together!
And be an
Idol!
Get together!
And be an
Idol!
Get together!
And be an
Idol!
Get together!
And be an
Idol!
Get together!
And be an
Idol!
Get together!
And be an
Idol!
Get together!
And be an
Idol!
Get together!
And be an
Idol!
Get together!
And be an
Idol!
Get together!
And be an
Idol!
Get together!
And be an
Idol!
Get together!
And be an
Idol!
Hey, you came to PriPara before, didn't you?
Get together!
Huh? Oh, yeah...
You should come by again.
And bring lots of friends!
And then you have to debut as an idol too!
Well...
There's only a café and photo studio,
so... I kinda got bored.
This isn't dreaming along well at all.
But I guess she's right –
there's not a lot of fun places in PriPara right now.
No matter where you Ji-go-ku...
the walls and the doors both have ears.
It's the Head Disciplinarian!
Don't worry! I thought something
like this might happen...
Cooking not yet complete.
I brought red beans instead of rice today!
Whoosh, whoosh!
Dearie me, it's as though I'm by the seashore.
Snip, snip, ship, snip...
Oh, I can hear it!
A little crab snip-snipping its pincers...
What kind of fool do you take me for?!
That got my dreams racing!
I think we lost her.
Oh, it's just you.
From the Cheerleading Club,
and the Sheep Squad, um...
It's Chiako.
I'm headed to Cheerleading Club practice now, got it?
Chia?
Your hair looks terrible.
Capisce...
Dreamy-cute...
Wow! We're even dreamy-cuter than normal!
You're incredible, Chiako!
It's nothing special.
Of course it is! You're a genius!
I just had a great idea!
Me too!
Chiako, come to PriPara with us.
Up we go!
Hey!
Let me down, you numskulls!
Hi there!
Welcome to Prism Stone.
Say, this is your first time, isn't it?
I only care about BoyPara, got it?
There's no point trying
to rope me into your PriPara thing.
We're not roping you into anything!
Hmph.
I bet if we harness your styling skills,
we can make an awesome shop here.
Fashion
Studio
Its name: Fashion Studio!
Studio... Studio... Studio...
We've gotta get PriPara
energised, you see! No matter what!
Won't you help us? Dreamy please?
We're begging you!
You numskulls don't know when to quit!
I'll forward on the request for a fashion studio.
Hey!
Knock... knock it off!
We got word from reception.
Your store's all ready for you!
Hooray!
I'm dreamless with anticipation!
Dreamy-cute!
We'll capture the hearts and dreams of the girls here!
What's wrong, Lala?
Take a look.
Are you dreaming kidding me?!
You haven't accrued any Idol Time,
so please make do with this!
Will we... really get any customers?
Incidentally, we have everything
Miss Chiako might need ready.
Hairstyle, hair colour... you can even change eye colour.
Though you'll need the right skills to use them properly.
What's this place?
Welcome!
This way, come right on in!
Our virtuosa beautician here
will give you a dreamy-cute makeover!
Um, you say she's a beautician...
but she looks like one of those stubborn old sushi chefs!
What kind of look are you going for?
Oh? Um, I guess I want it in a fringe,
with waves so it moves in layers.
Mm.
Mm-hm.
For the makeup, I was thinking arched eyebrows,
with a matte look for the lipstick.
And then...
Quit spouting industry jargon
when you look like a fashion disaster.
Excuse me?
You got a problem, you're free to go.
H-Hey, you can't say that...
I'm so sorry!
But her skills are the real deal, you know...
Bring your face over here.
There, done and done.
Wow, you're so dreamy-cute!
Is this really me?
Hmph. It's an improvement from before, that's for sure.
Miss stubborn beautician, could you do me next?
Me too!
Me three!
Me four!
Now there's a whole crowd!
All right! Lala, we'd better help out too!
Next in line, right this way!
Punicorn!
Pamper my skin like at a risotto!
Dreamy-cute!
Capisce!
Punicorn.
Feel the love, my darling.
All done!
Ah, the love, it is... so heavy.
Puni.
Oh no, it boiled over.
Huh?
U-Um, it sure has been raining a lot recently, huh?
Shut up.
What?
She's incredible.
She's pretty scary, but she'll make you really cute.
Sit down and shut up.
Numskulls.
The fashion studio's a huge hit.
And so...
Fashion Studio
You've been upgraded from floor matting to a shack!
Huzzah!
Punicorn!
Walls and a roof!
Hmph. It's still a heap of garbage.
I guess we're friends after today, huh, Chiako?
Thanks a dream for today!
You really helped us out.
Well, it was a royal pain in the neck for me.
There you go again...
You don't want to admit it,
but you had fun, didn't you?
I wonder if maybe you want to be a beautician one day.
Ooh, bullseye!
PriPara's a place where girls' dreams come true!
Girls'... dreams?
I'll support your dream with all my dreams, Chiako!
Me too!
Do whatever you want.
Chiako.
You skipped practice. What were you doing?
Oh, sorry.
No, she wasn't skipping.
We kinda dragged her to PriPara
to do some hairstyling and makeup work.
PriPara?!
Chiako, do I have to remind you?
The Cheerleading Club was formed
for the purpose of cheering on BoyPara.
And you're casting aside BoyPara to go to PriPara?
That won't do!
Don't think I'm sad or anything
that you chose PriPara over us, okay?
It's not like that.
It's just...
Will you choose friendship or PriPara?
It's one or the other.
Well, maybe I don't need either.
Chiako!
What's her problem?
Well, that put a damper on things.
Let's hurry up and go to BoyPara.
Come on, let's go!
We've still got time before curfew...
Let's go, BoyPara!
I'm going to talk with Aiko and the others.
Come on, come on, BoyPara!
Let's go, BoyPara!
Got it. Then I'll go after Chiako.
Come on, come on, BoyPara!
I'm telling you, it wasn't Chiako's fault.
Okay? You should all come to PriPara too.
And you'll realise how fun it is too.
No, thank you!
I'm capisce baa-gging you!
For the last time, this is a sheep's...
Baa!
Chiako! I'm real sorry!
It's not your fault.
I'm sure they'll understand if you tell them
being a beautician's your dream.
Hmph! I never said I cared about that stuff.
That's not true! If it is, what about that?
You're the one who beautified
all these plants, aren't you?
Leave me alone already!
Morning.
Morning!
So as I was saying...
How did things end up this way?
It's because Chiako doesn't care about us.
I reckon.
But Chiako did always like
giving people makeovers and stuff, didn't she?
I-It's not like I care about
making up with her or anything.
There has to be a way to set this straight...
It's totally time!
Check out these babies! Shougo, they look totally great!
They're freakin' rad!
Asahi, you're so totally rad!
Ooh, a little octopus wiener.
Down the hatch you go!
I made that, Shougo!
This miso soup is delectable.
I love the night moon.
Hey, I know! If I can get the members of WITH
to talk to the Sheep Squad...
Fighting's ain't rad at all!
Nothing good comes from conflict and strife.
If you make up, I'll give you a special hug!
Hug with you.
Baa!
Yep, I'm sure they'll make up!
I'll just go and ask them...
Not another dream!
Why not?
I won't dream a word of it!
I'd rather suck rice through my nostrils
than bow and scrape to my brother!
Seriously?
Fashion Studio
I thought the WITH strategy was a pretty good one too.
No way, no how! We'll think of something else!
Miss Yui, Miss Lala.
How are your recruitment efforts going?
Ulp.
The fashion studio's closed today,
so visitors are on the decline.
What?
This is bad news!
We're teetering on the edge of the abyss!
That's right.
The Grand Prix's so soon –
we don't have time for stuff like this.
But friends are more important than anything else!
I want Chiako and her friends to smile,
no matter what happens!
Yeah, you're right!
Fashion Studio
A fashion studio...
Hairstyling and makeup...
That's it!
Chiako.
Give us your decision.
What matters to you more, friendship or PriPara?
Wowee! Look, the guys from WITH are here!
What?
Hey girls.
I heard all about the situation.
And I totally...
Capisce!
You should totally let us give you advice!
We care about you all, you know.
From a sunrise
to night stars yonder,
together we can show you it all!
Wowee, they're so cool and amazing!
See? WITH came to see you and everything.
Shouldn't you all just make up?
We'll continue this where no idiots can interfere.
No, wait just a capisce!
I can't choose.
Friendship, PriPara...
Of course, you're all really important to me.
But...
PriPara's a place where dreams can come true.
So if you tell me to choose one...
I don't even know myself.
You should come and see Chiako in PriPara.
We should all go and support her together.
It's what Chiako's
dreameehing about!
That baa just now...
was pure sheep!
It was?
Baa...
-cause of that display of respect,
Chiako.
You shall style us in PriPara.
Style you...
And just which you should choose,
friendship or PriPara...
We will give the proper judgement.
Welcome!
We'll register you into PriPara
with Miss Chiako's styling, then?
Then, if you would all scan after Miss Chiako.
We've arranged it so your PriPara Change
will be as per Miss Chiako's design.
It's the system!
Oh my...
Amazing.
I almost didn't recognise myself.
I-It's not like I'm happy you
made me this cute or anything.
Fashion Studio
Hey, it's the stubborn stylist!
Can you please do my hair too?
Me too! Please do me as well!
Bring your faces over here.
I think we have an answer.
You should choose Friendship and PriPara.
Chiako, you've got a real eye for styling!
You can keep going to BoyPara,
and we'll support your dream here too.
I – I guess you can go to PriPara too, okay?
Girls...
All right!
It's so wonderful you were able
to strengthen your bonds with your friends.
And furthermore,
our visitor count is on the rise as well!
Wow!
Puni!
And so,
Miss Yui and Miss Lala's
Idol Time has been maxed out!
You can now give a three-minute performance!
Do your best and aim
to increase visitor numbers even more!
Puni!
Punicorn!
Scan the appropriate number
of My Tickets for your outfit.
You can also scan each other's Friend Tickets.
Countdown to Idol Time!
For a duet performance, it's gotta be
matching outfits in different colours!
Rabbit Heart Fancy Ensemble!
With a pastel-coloured clock accessory on the chest,
it feels like the White Rabbit
come to take us to Wonderland!
Rabbit Heart Mint Ensemble!
Start!
Dreaming, dreaming days
dreaming dreaming days
Such exciting days (Oh yeah!)
wakuwaku days (oh yeah)
Nothing standing in our way
nevagiba days
Are you ready now?
junbi all ok
Dreaming, dreaming days
dreaming dreaming days
Such exciting days (Oh yeah!)
wakuwaku days (oh yeah)
Are you daydreaming?
yumetteru
Open my future!
open my future
Remember when it all seemed so dull?
dokidoki ga umareteku
Then it set our hearts aflutter
shunkan ni fureta toki
A whole new world unfolded for us
hajimete no sekai ga matteta no
Colours pastel cute and vivid bright
pasuteru mo bibiddo mo
I love them all so much I can't choose
suteki da mon nayanjau
How do we feel, making a heart shape together?
donna fuu ni kokoro katachi ni shiyou
Thoughts keep on welling up
afureru think about sorezore
So many shades of happiness
toridori no happiness
If we layer them, can we bring about a miracle?
kasanattara okiru kiseki ga aru no
We're making a brand new dream (Woo-hoo!)
making making brand new na yume ga (fuffuu)
Like a popping dance right now (Dance! Dance!)
poppin poppin odoridasu mitai (dance dance)
You and me in harmony
kimi to no haamonii
Pushing each other on and on and on
butsukariatte shinkouchuu
We're not gonna give in
makenai
We wanna see
mitemitai
Our future = Dreamy-cute x Capisce! (Hey!)
mirai yumekawa kashikoma (ne)
Making Drama, switch on!
Lala!
Yui!
You and me!
Let's go!
No, you won't be perfect right from the start
ikinari sugoi wake ja nai
Dreamy-cute!
Capisce!
But you've already got everything you need
dakedo ne chanto motteru yo
Our encounter...
...must be fate!
You've got the ticket to take that very first step
saisho no ippo he no chiketto wo
A fateful first meeting!
Girl meets girl!
I can't sit still, I've gotta get ready (Yes, yes!)
sowasowa yoi wo shinakucha (yes yes)
Cyalume Time!
Let's unlock the door and with it our hearts (Open!)
doa to haato no kagi akete (open)
That's where it all begins
sou shitara hajimacchau
Three, two, one – welcome to Idol Time
three two one youkoso aidoru taimu
Dreamy-cute!
Capisce!
Today is pure, blank and waiting (Woo-hoo!)
pyua pyua massara no kyou ga (fuffuu)
We can paint whatever colour we want (Wow! Wow!)
change change irozuiteku yo (wao wao)
So what happens now?
koko kara dou naru no
Well, the fun's in finding out!
dekiagari wa otanoshimi
You and me
issho ni ne
We can do it together
tsukucchaou
Our hopes = Dreamy-cute x Capisce! (And...)
kitai yumekawa kashikoma (de)
Our future = Dreamy-cute x Capisce! (Hey!)
mirai yumekawa kashikoma (ne)
Dreaming, dreaming days
dreaming dreaming days
Such exciting days (Oh yeah!)
wakuwaku days (oh yeah)
Nothing standing in our way
nevagiba days
Are you ready now?
junbi all ok
Dreaming, dreaming days
dreaming dreaming days
Such exciting days (Oh yeah!)
wakuwaku days (oh yeah)
Are you daydreaming?
yumetteru
Open our future!
open our future
Dreamy-cute x Capisce!
yumekawa kashikoma
Miss Yui! You're so dreamy-cute!
I like you quite a bit!
You were splendid!
That was so cute!
That rocked!
I guess I was excited and stuff!
That was pretty good, got it?
Fashion Studio
The fashion studio is now officially open!
Well, cook me dead!
Miss Chiako, will you sign on officially
as a beautician here in PriPara?
She graciously accepts.
Isn't that great, Chiako?
I'm gonna work hard with PriPara,
BoyPara and cheerleading!
All right!
Mm, this is getting really exciting now!
You five sure share a dreamyful friendship!
Oh? You seem to be forgetting you two.
Huh?
Us too?
That's kinda dreambarrassing...
Yui! We need lots more girls to start being idols,
so let's keep at it!
Yeah!
Huff, puff, yo!
What, really?
Huff, puff... huh?
Yep, there's a fashion studio in PriPara now!
It looks awesome!
We should go together.
That sounds great!
We're doing it!
Huff, puff, yo!
Next Episode
Nino, dreamy please!
Come be an idol with us in PriPara!
No marks for that idea!
'Sides, today there's an event I'm helping with
at the Paparajuku shopping arcade!
An event at the shopping arcade?
That's it! We can set up a shop to promote PriPara!
I capisce that idea a hundred percent!
Yui, Lala... you're really on fire there!
What's PriPara... What're idols really about?
Next time, Yo, I Became A Helper Idol!
Yo, I Became
A Helper Idol!
Come on, everyone! It's time to be an idol!