It's Mirei and Lala's show from the other day!
Mm, I like it!
Isn't PriPara wonderful?
No matter where you Ji-go-ku...
the walls and the doors both have ears.
The two of you just said
PriPara was wonderful, did you not?
Head Disciplinarian Jigoku?
There's dreamy hell in store for us if she catches us!
Our Avocado Academy girls have no use for PriPara!
Now begone from my sight!
How scary! And stewy!
A-here I am, sailing away, gondola with the wind...
Gondola with the wind...
Going to Paparajuku, huh...
I don't know if I can bear it.
Manager Training
for Punicorn-kuma!
Wow, so many of you came along!
Thank you! This is like a dream come true!
Puni!
But there still aren't that many...
Punicorn.
Punicorn's smile is telling us to cheer up.
"Give your best during today's dance lessons,
so you can give a performance
that makes all the girls want to come to PriPara."
Okay!
Puni!
It's done cookin', warm and fresh!
Down the dreamin' hatch!
Dreaming delish!
Punicorn, can you reserve a room
for practice after we're done eating?
Punicorn?
She looks kinda confused.
Punicorn, do you know what a manager does?
Punicorn!
That's it! You've gotta set off
for dreamland with a nap after eating!
Think I'll join you...
Hey, that's not right!
What?
Then let it steam!
Do you really not know what a manager does, Punicorn?
Punicorn.
What?
Shoebill's home delivery service!
We deliver your packages
with the energy of love and smiles-kuma!
Thank you very much.
Hey, is that Kuma?
Oh, hi Lala-kuma.
Whatcha doing here?
W-Well, duh-kuma!
I was worried you were slacking off,
so I came to see you-kuma!
Wow, thanks!
Hey, that's great timing.
So these are my friends.
I'm the dreamy-cute Yumekawa Yui...
and this is my manager Punicorn!
Pleased to dream you!
Punicorn!
Punicorn popped out of an egg not too long ago
and doesn't really understand being a manager.
Ku... ma...
That design has so many lines-kuma.
So it'd be great if you could help her out, Kuma.
Um... are you listening?
Kuma!
You can leave it all to little old me-kuma!
I'll hammer the ABCs of being
a manager into you right quick-kuma!
Capisce!
Dreamy-cute!
Isn't that great, Punicorn?
Punicorn!
I see, I see. So that's why
Paparajuku's PriPara is so bear...
Well, that's when managers
need to step up and take charge-kuma!
A real veteran can handle anything, you know-kuma!
So... why are you getting mad?
This newbie runt's shining eyes tick me off-kuma!
Look at all the lines!
And they're oh-so-carefully drawn-kuma!
There's a world of difference between us-kuma!
Punicorn!
Hey, newbie here just laughed at me-kuma!
It makes my blood boil, my stomach churn!
No, Punicorn's just always smiling.
My poor, empty stomach – I'm starved-kuma!
Kuma, I'm capis-counting on you!
Dreamy-cuting on you!
Hrm... all right-kuma.
After all, it was ol' me here who raised
SoLaMi SMILE up to be Divine Idols
I'm a Divine Manager, you know, and I'm finally
about to move into a 20-room apartment-kuma!
Divine Manager?
Here's my card-kuma.
Divine manager
Divine
Klaus Henrik Poncetta Von Vogel Strobel Cash De La Manecca the Third
Divine manager
Divine
Klaus Henrik Poncetta Von Vogel Strobel Cash De La Manecca the Third
Divine manager
Divine
Klaus Henrik Poncetta Von Vogel Strobel Cash De La Manecca the Third
Divine manager
Divine
Klaus Henrik Poncetta Von Vogel Strobel Cash De La Manecca the Third
Divine manager
Divine
Klaus Henrik Poncetta Von Vogel Strobel Cash De La Manecca the Third
Divine manager
Divine
Klaus Henrik Poncetta Von Vogel Strobel Cash De La Manecca the Third
Divine manager
Divine
Klaus Henrik Poncetta Von Vogel Strobel Cash De La Manecca the Third
Divine manager
Divine
Klaus Henrik Poncetta Von Vogel Strobel Cash De La Manecca the Third
Divine manager
Divine
Klaus Henrik Poncetta Von Vogel Strobel Cash De La Manecca the Third
Divine manager
Divine
Klaus Henrik Poncetta Von Vogel Strobel Cash De La Manecca the Third
Divine manager
Divine
Klaus Henrik Poncetta Von Vogel Strobel Cash De La Manecca the Third
Divine manager
Divine
Klaus Henrik Poncetta Von Vogel Strobel Cash De La Manecca the Third
Divine manager
Divine
Klaus Henrik Poncetta Von Vogel Strobel Cash De La Manecca the Third
Divine manager
Divine
Klaus Henrik Poncetta Von Vogel Strobel Cash De La Manecca the Third
Divine manager
Divine
Klaus Henrik Poncetta Von Vogel Strobel Cash De La Manecca the Third
Divine manager
Divine
Klaus Henrik Poncetta Von Vogel Strobel Cash De La Manecca the Third
Divine manager
Divine
Klaus Henrik Poncetta Von Vogel Strobel Cash De La Manecca the Third
Divine manager
Divine
Klaus Henrik Poncetta Von Vogel Strobel Cash De La Manecca the Third
Divine manager
Divine
Klaus Henrik Poncetta Von Vogel Strobel Cash De La Manecca the Third
Divine manager
Divine
Klaus Henrik Poncetta Von Vogel Strobel Cash De La Manecca the Third
Divine manager
Divine
Klaus Henrik Poncetta Von Vogel Strobel Cash De La Manecca the Third
Divine manager
Divine
Klaus Henrik Poncetta Von Vogel Strobel Cash De La Manecca the Third
Divine manager
Divine
Klaus Henrik Poncetta Von Vogel Strobel Cash De La Manecca the Third
Divine manager
Divine
Klaus Henrik Poncetta Von Vogel Strobel Cash De La Manecca the Third
Divine manager
Divine
Klaus Henrik Poncetta Von Vogel Strobel Cash De La Manecca the Third
Divine manager
Divine
Klaus Henrik Poncetta Von Vogel Strobel Cash De La Manecca the Third
Divine manager
Divine
Klaus Henrik Poncetta Von Vogel Strobel Cash De La Manecca the Third
Divine manager
Divine
Klaus Henrik Poncetta Von Vogel Strobel Cash De La Manecca the Third
Divine manager
Divine
Klaus Henrik Poncetta Von Vogel Strobel Cash De La Manecca the Third
Divine manager
Divine
Klaus Henrik Poncetta Von Vogel Strobel Cash De La Manecca the Third
Divine manager
Divine
Klaus Henrik Poncetta Von Vogel Strobel Cash De La Manecca the Third
Divine manager
Divine
Klaus Henrik Poncetta Von Vogel Strobel Cash De La Manecca the Third
Divine manager
Divine
Klaus Henrik Poncetta Von Vogel Strobel Cash De La Manecca the Third
My name, you see,
is Klaus Henrik Poncetta Von Vogel – oh...
Divine manager
Divine
There's no such position as "Divine Manager".
Please don't make false documentation.
No! I gave up veggie juice and saved
my pocket money for three months for that-kuma!
Kuma, you're so funny!
Punicorn!
Grr!
You're sorely mistaken if you think you can make it
in this world with just a cute smile-kuma!
You're gonna get educated, you hear-kuma?
What a kum-erfuffle!
We'll begin with how to scout a promising idol-kuma!
Hey, ladies – your names?
I'm Lala!
I'm Yui!
Punicorn.
Everyone in sight's part of the gang-kuma...
Isn't there anyone else around-kuma?
It's just sad to see a PriPara without idols-kuma.
Oof!
Dream!
Punicorn.
Thanks, Punicorn. You're so kind.
Actually, since we're already here,
I don't think Punicorn needs to scout anyone else!
Oh yeah, good point.
Pu-Pu-Pu-Pu-Pu-Pu!
Next up!
When you've scouted an idol,
but they're not coming to PriPara...
"Ow-ow-ow! My head hurts!
My heart pangs, and my teeth ache –
you have to come-kuma!"
Bug them to come back,
even if you hafta use crocodile tears-kuma!
Give it a try-kuma.
Punicorn.
Punicorn, punicorn.
Punicorn, punicorn. Puni–
Hey, we can't understand a word you're saying-kuma!
But it's so cute!
Don't worry, Punicorn, I'll be there in a flash!
You two are way too soft on the kid-kuma!
Punicorn... Punicorn, punicorn...
Wow, anything Punicorn does is dreamy-cute!
So true!
That's all wrong!
Punicorn, aim to be a cool gentleman
like yours truly-kuma.
Punicorn.
Whoa, that took me by surprise-kuma...
Um, Kuma, about Punicorn...
She's a dreamy-cute girl, you know.
Say wha-at?
Oh, is that the case-kuma?
Then I finally have a little sister of my own-kuma...
Punicorn, you can call me "Big Bro" if you want-kuma...
Pu...
You can call me "Big Bro" if you want-kuma...
Puni...
Punicorn!
That was a sneeze?!
Ah-choo!
Idol
Dojo
Cooky
Idol
Dojo
Cooky
Idol
Dojo
Cooky
Idol
Dojo
Cooky
Idol
Dojo
Kuma's
Cooky
Idol
Dojo
Kuma's
Idol
Dojo
Kuma's
Idol
Dojo
Kuma's
We're now starting intermediate manager lessons-kuma!
It's only gonna get harsher from here,
so get ready-kuma!
Idol
Idol Dojo
One, two! One, two!
You two, match your steps to the tempo
and look straight ahead as you walk-kuma!
Now, Punicorn, you give it a try-kuma.
Puni...
You need a firm hand for idol training-kuma.
Punicorn.
Puni...
corn!
Thanks, Punicorn!
Puni...
corn!
We'll keep it up!
Puni...
corn!
That's good-kuma! Keep up the pace-kuma! Yeah...
Puni...
corn!
Punicorn...
Kuma?
Are you okay?
Ow-ow...kuma-ma...
Punicorn...
Pun...
Well... just be bearful, newbie...
What a kum-erfuffle!
This machine trains your handshake abilities-kuma.
Lala trained with this baby
when she was a newbie idol-kuma!
It feels like so long ago!
Yui, you'll be training hard as well-kuma!
Dreampisce!
And... start her up-kuma!
Thanks a dream! Thanks a dream!
That's the spirit-kuma!
Thanks a dream! Thanks a dream! Thanks...
Puni-puni-puni!
Okay, Punicorn! Now you try-kuma!
Punicorn.
Thanks a dream! Thanks a dream!
Now speed it up-kuma!
Puni...
corn!
Hey – isn't this too fast?
I can handle it like a dream!
That's it – idols and managers
working hard together-kuma!
Yeah!
Punicorn!
Puni.
Kuma!
Puni...
corn!
Kuma, are you all right?
All right?
Course I'm not-kuma!
Getting smacked around like that
will destroy my rugged good looks-kuma!
Ol' me's going home.
I'm sorry! But I think I really learned about hand-shaking!
Thank you, Kuma! Thank you, Punicorn!
Pu... pu...
Punicorn.
Aw, come on... Very well, but this is it!
This is the most vital, but it comes down to basics.
Before I leave, I'll teach you
how to reserve the stage-kuma.
Okay! Thank you, Kuma.
Let's do it, Punicorn!
Punicorn!
For a manager to get to registration
first and reserve the best stage,
they need mental and physical strength-kuma!
Today we're aiming for that red number 10 room-kuma!
When Meganee confirms you have an "entry",
you've got it-kuma!
Punicorn.
Usually there's fierce competition to reserve a stage,
but since there's no one else around,
you'll be racing Yui and Lala to the desk-kuma!
Dreamy-cute!
Capisce!
Keep running, no matter what happens.
That's a path to being a true manager-kuma!
Punicorn.
On your marks...
get set...
go-kuma!
Make way for cleaning!
What?
Ah! It's so slippery!
Punicorn? Punicorn?
Punicorn?
Thank you!
Hey there!
I told you to keep running,
no matter what happens-kuma...
Punicorn.
Pu... Pu...
Pu... Pu... Pu...
Punicorn! Punicorn! Punicorn!
Pu-pu-pu-pu-punicorn!
Punicorn-corn!
Hey, are those wings of yours
for decoration or what-kuma?
Puni-puni-punicorn, punicorn!
Puni... Punicorn! Punicorn! Puni-punicorn!
"Keep running, no matter what happens"...
Puni-puni-punicorn! Punicorn!
Isn't that what you told her?
What?
Punicorn! Puni-ni-ni... Punicorn!
You're allowed to fly-kuma.
Puni.
Punicorn! Punicorn!
Puni-punicorn-corn, puni-punicorn!
An entry for the red number 10? Most certainly!
The stage is reserved for your show.
Punicorn.
What a great kid-kuma!
You really tried hard, Punicorn!
You were totally dreamy-cute!
Congratulations!
After working hard at her manager training,
Miss Punicorn has deepened her relationship
with Miss Lala and Miss Yui,
and their Idol Time has been maxed out.
Both of you can now give a three-minute performance!
Wow!
All right!
All thanks to my guidance-kuma!
Thank you, Kuma!
Scan the appropriate number
of My Tickets for your outfit.
Countdown to Idol Time!
The badge emblems and patches give it a burst of colour!
The black highlights give it a cool feel as well!
Happy Emblem Cherry Ensemble!
Start!
Stop trying to be like that other girl
oshare na ano ko mane suru yori
You're already the number-one girl you can be
jibunrashisa ga ichiban desho
Can't you feel it in your heart?
haato no kagayaki kanjita nara
Let's go look for our own ideals
risou sagashi ni dekakeyou yo
And every single memory we make
fueteiku omoide zenbu
We'll snap in two and
pakin to hanbunko de
Complete the set with our friends
tomodachi konpuriito shiyou
Make it! You're unbeatable once you get started
make it doki doki suru toki muteki desho
Make up! Headed for a gloriously shining future
make up kira kira mirai de kimari desho
Your dreams aren't out of reach
yume wa mou yume ja nai
Making Drama, switch on!
Anyone can make theirs come true
dare datte kanaerareru
Lady! Ready to go – to paradise!
redi ready to go paradise
Twirling!
Exciting!
Deliver it to everyone!
Make it – I don't ever want to let go of this dream
make it akirametakunai yume dakara
Present for you!
Make up – I don't want to give it up before I even start
make up akogare no mama ja iya dakara
Cyalume Time!
Make up – I don't want to give it up before I even start
make up akogare no mama ja iya dakara
Make it! You're unbeatable once you get started
make it doki doki suru toki muteki desho
Capisce!
Make up! You're headed for a gloriously shining future
make up kira kira mirai de kimari desho
Your dreams aren't out of reach
yume wa mou yume ja nai
Anyone can make theirs come true
dare datte kanaerareru
PriPara Pri-paradise
puripara puriparadaisu
I love your face, Miss Lala!
You're so cute, Lala!
Puni!
Punicorn!
An outfit from the brand Miss Yui designed, Fantasy Time.
The sky-blue and pink colour
combination fits beautifully!
Magical Star Pink Ensemble!
Start!
Dreamy cute to the capisce max!
Tick-tock magicalun-lun - Idol Time starts now!
chikutaku magica runrun aidoru taimu sutaato
Come on!
kamon
(Magical! Idol! Here we go!)
(majikaru aidoru here we go)
It's the magic girls long for
onna no ko ga akogaretekita mahou
Do not watch!
A splendorous world where mysteries abound
fushigi wa joushiki chouisekai
You must not look.
Cast your eyes aside, I say!
I cast my spell and it's showtime
tonaetara shoutaimu
Disguise yourself if you will – you cannot fool my ears.
All I need is a little transformation and I'm ready
henshin shitara junbi bacchiri da yo
They've entered PriPara from somewhere,
and I will find out where!
I feel like Cinderella
marude kibun wa shinderera
Beckoned secretly to the ball
kossori goshoutai
I'd better hurry up, cause everyone's waiting - no, no more limits
sore ja isogou minna matteru kitto anrimiteddo
Now the future is boundless
saa mirai eigou
Mark this moment in time!
toki o kizamu yo
(Tick-tock magical go!)
(chikutaku magikaru go)
Now hold on just a moment? I can't stop! Here, with my mic in hand
chotto jasutamoomen tomaranai yo maiku katate ni
Taking the hour hand and dancing, my heart singing
tanshin to dancing kokoro singing
In a thrilling singularity
tokimeki shingyuraritii
The mystery of the unclear is so entrancing
katachi no nai mono koso itsudatte hoshii yo
Music holds my hopes, so pretty and sweet
kibou to myuujikku puriti kyuuti
When I'm so excited I can't hold still
dokidoki machikirenai nara
Tick-tock magicalun-lun - it's Idol Time, and we're not done!
chikutaku magica runrun aidoru taimu tsuzuku yo
Is it a dream or reflection, truth or illusion? Who can say?
yume ka utsusu ka uso ka hontou ka dare mo wakaranai
Making Drama, switch on!
Adrift in the ebb and flow of time and space
watashi dake jikan fuuyuu kuukan
Until eternal twilight blooms
towairaito ga terasu made
Like a dream, dreamy-cute!
Tick-tock super Idol Time!
chikutaku super idol time
Tick and tock and
chii-ku ta-ku
Now just a moment, I hold my secrets always in my heart
jasutamoomen zutto zutto himitsu o mune ni
Whee!
In the loveliest outfit, in a single breath
saikou no koode wanburesu de
It's dreamcredible: welcome to dreamland!
Awakened by dream energy
mezameru doriimu enajii
Dreamy-cute Magical Clock Land!
The mystery of the unclear is so entrancing
katachi no nai mono koso itsudatte hoshii yo
Music holds my hopes, so pretty and sweet
kibou to myuujikku puriti kyuuti
Cyalume Time!
When I'm so excited I can't hold still
dokidoki machikirenai nara
Tick tock, I've gotta take it
chikutaku ima toraete
That chance comes just the once!
chansu wa isshun dake yo
Dreamy-cute!
Tick-tock magicalun-lun, now Idol Time: da capo!
chikutaku magica runrun aidoru taimu da kaapo
It's dreamy-lovely!
Miss Yui, look this way!
You did great, Yui!
You too, Lala!
Puni?
What's that sound?
Punicorn!
Huh?
Punicorn, where are you going?
Wait up, Punicorn!
This path leads to the clock tower, doesn't it?
Punicorn!
Punicorn?
No good – it won't open!
Punicorn, punicorn!
What lovely music.
Yeah, it's enchanting.
Punicorn.
Pu.
Punicorn!
Where did you run off to?
Punicorn.
I dream that much, at least.
That reminds me, Punicorn,
you came out of an egg that shot out
of the clock tower, didn't you?
Did that have something to do with the music just now?
Punicorn!
That smile doesn't tell us anything!
Come on...
How dare they finish up their show
without coming to see me-kuma!
Hello, this is Kuma-kuma!
Oh, Boss! Yes, I've finished the delivery
and I'm coming back now-kuma!
What great timing.
I have a same-day delivery to Parajuku for you.
If it's not delivered in 90 minutes,
there's a 10,000 coin penalty!
O-Okay-kuma...
Farewell, o ungrateful Paparajuku-kuma!
Wait up!
You're going back, Kuma?
You know it-kuma!
Can't have you ladies falling for me-kuma!
Punicorn!
Punicorn, punicorn, punicorn, punicorn, punicorn!
Punicorn, punicorn, punicorn!
Punicorn's dreaming her thanks for you!
Yep!
I know that-kuma!
Ol' me here hereby recognises you
as my number one idol apprentice-kuma!
I leave Lala and Yui in your capable hooves-kuma!
Punicorn!
And I'll be rooting for you too-kuma!
Thanks a dream!
Stay safe until we meet again!
Punicorn!
I'll be back!
Okay! Now Punicorn's all learned up on being a manager.
Let's keep dreaming our best
until the Idol Time Grand Prix!
Capisce!
Hey, wasn't he wearing the
Shoebill Delivery Service uniform?
What's that about?
Mr Kuma was causing no end of trouble in Parajuku,
so he was stripped of his manager position.
Now he's working for Shoebill Delivery Service!
What?
Pu?
What the dream?
It's not easy being a manager-kuma!
Punicorn.
Kuma...
Ol' Kuma's never gonna give up-kuma!
Oh, I give up...
Next Episode
Man, PriPara's still not getting a lot of new idols...
Even though BoyPara's a party every day...
It really dreams my goat!
Hey, Yui, let's go to BoyPara!
We can check out a concert
and find out what's so amazing!
What? No way in dreams!
I don't wanna see my dumb brother in his idol getup!
Come on, it's all for PriPara!
We'll join the Sheep Squad
and then it's let's go BoyPara!
Next time, Dreamy-Dreamy?! Infiltrate BoyPara!
Dreamy-Dreamy?!
Infiltrate BoyPara!
Come on, everyone! It's time to be an idol!