Yui...
I've said this whole time that
little girls could never be idols...
Who ever heard of a girl idol?
You trying to embarrass me?
Don't do something so lame ever again, got it?
But I was wrong...
Compared to your perfect performance,
my singing may as well be a stray cat burping!
Meow-urp.
I don't deserve to be an idol...
Don't say that.
If you dream your hardest, you can shine
dreamy-bright-but-not-as-bright-as-me, I'm sure!
If you call it quits here, the concert's already over!
I want to be an idol!
What a dream! A dream, a dream, a dream...
Yui.
Hey, Yui.
Dream?
Puni.
Huh?
Hey, where'd my brother go? And my fans?
Fans?
You and your delusions!
There are a few more girls coming to PriPara now...
Sneak, sneak...
Hey, want to try performing?
Girls being idols...
That'd be mortifying!
Dreamy...
At this rate, we won't get a single new idol
debuting before the Grand Prix in June...
Puni.
All right! Let's give this a shot!
Your Idol Time is currently full.
You can give a three-minute performance!
I'm gonna use the Idol Time
from my day-to-day recruiting
and heat things up with a show!
Dreamy-Dreamy?!
Infiltrate BoyPara!
Scan the appropriate number
of My Tickets for your outfit.
Countdown to Idol Time!
According to Meganee research,
99.99% of girls coming to PriPara love this outfit!
Happy Emblem Cherry Ensemble!
Start!
Miss Lala!
Wonderful as always!
Watch my show, everyone,
and fall even more in love with PriPara!
Stop trying to be like that other girl
oshare na ano ko mane suru yori
You're already the number-one girl you can be
jibunrashisa ga ichiban desho
Can't you feel it in your heart?
haato no kagayaki kanjita nara
Let's go look for our own ideals
risou sagashi ni dekakeyou yo
And every single memory we make
fueteiku omoide zenbu
We'll snap in two and
pakin to hanbunko de
Complete the set with our friends
tomodachi konpuriito shiyou
Make it! You're unbeatable once you get started
make it doki doki suru toki muteki desho
Make up! Headed for a gloriously shining future
make up kira kira mirai de kimari desho
Your dreams aren't out of reach
yume wa mou yume ja nai
Making Drama, switch on!
Anyone can make theirs come true
dare datte kanaerareru
Rain...
Lady! Ready to go – to paradise!
redi ready to go paradise
Look up at the sky...
and smile!
Hello!
Make it – I don't ever want to let go of this dream
make it akirametakunai yume dakara
Blue-sky Smile Sparkling!
Make up – I don't want to give it up before I even start
make up akogare no mama ja iya dakara
Cyalume Time!
Make up – I don't want to give it up before I even start
make up akogare no mama ja iya dakara
Make it! You're unbeatable once you get started
make it doki doki suru toki muteki desho
Capisce!
Make up! You're headed for a gloriously shining future
make up kira kira mirai de kimari desho
Your dreams aren't out of reach
yume wa mou yume ja nai
Anyone can make theirs come true
dare datte kanaerareru
PriPara Pri-paradise
puripara puriparadaisu
Miss Lala!
You're so lovely!
Perfect to a capisce, if I do say so myself!
That was dreamy-lovely!
She's not a Divine Idol for nothing!
I'd love to be an amazing idol like that one day.
But...
There's no way we could do it.
Hey, BoyPara TV's starting soon!
Gotta run!
Hey, wait a dream!
Wait for us!
Cooking completed.
Jeez!
Why doesn't anyone understand?
PriPara's a million times dreamier than dumb BoyPara!
It's enough to make a girl doubt her Divine Idolhood...
Actually, what are BoyPara concerts like, anyway?
The idols and the audience members are all boys, right?
Are they kind of like Hibiki?
Or maybe...
It's not like this, is it?
I'm kind of curious now.
Then you should totally watch one!
Check out the number one group, WITH,
and you'll learn what BoyPara's all about!
You think so?
Why not? Let's join up with the Sheep Squad,
sneak in and check it out in person!
Nuh-uh.
That doesn't interest me one bit.
I don't want to see my dumb brother performing.
How about some yummy pri-easoning for your rice there.
Huh?
Lead the way.
No matter where you Ji-go-ku...
my ears'll hear you.
What was that?
Now they're trying to infiltrate BoyPara?
BoyPara is verboten for womankind!
It is an Eden for those beautiful and unsullied males!
I too yearn to enter that bar-bidden land,
but I bar-bear it, bar-break my heart as it does!
Oh, it's simply barbarous!
To uphold the order of this academy,
you must discover their point of entry and intercept them!
We are...
...the Sheep Squad!
We have some new members today.
Our arms are open to new comrades.
Y-You can join us, I guess.
We'll start introductory training right away, got it?
Listen to me: baa!
Baa!
That's a bleating goat cry!
Y-You'd better sheep up or ship out, you hear!
To infiltrate BoyPara, where girls are not allowed,
we must keep in mind...
Number one...
...and number two:
to become a sheep, mind and soul!
There are no ingredients for rice.
My stomach's dreameehing empty.
What's the point of this?
If I just perform well enough to dream their socks off,
PriPara will get plenty energised, dreameeh.
Sniff, sniff.
Hey, I smell some dreameeh delicious rice!
Sniff, sniff, sniff-sniff.
I smell a tempura rice ball! How dreameeh!
Wha– Shougo?
Yui?
That outfit suits you way more than being an idol does!
Dreamy grr!
It does not!
And you were the one crying
and begging me and Misae
to let you play house with us at the Kobayashis' place!
Ulp.
How about I show this to everyone!
I'll get you for that!
Oh, actually, did you want some of my tempura rice ball?
Sure, I'll dream some!
Tempura
Rice Ball
Nom.
Dreameeh...
I'll dream you real good for that one, Shougo!
Yui...
where'd you go to?
She must have been unable to take our training and fled.
Now, let's set off for BoyPara!
No matter where you Ji-go-ku...
the walls and the doors both have ears.
Jigoku Mimiko stands before you.
Sneak, sneak.
I'm certain I heard "BoyPara" spoken around here...
Are you not the Sheep Squad, who disguise themselves
as sheep to try and infiltrate BoyPara?
Baa.
What's that?
I seem to have heard one goat-like cry among the flock.
Baa.
Why don't you try baaing one more time?
And I'll most assuredly uncover your
secret route into BoyPara and PriPara.
What should I do?
She's gonna find out for sure!
In through the front door, around the baa-ck.
Deny me my rice ball? Time for paybaack.
Yui?
Well, aren't you the suspicious one.
Why don't you speak up and admit your guilt?
You will not baa my way.
You will not baa my BoyPara dreamfiltration!
I cannae hear anything!
Get dreameeh, hurry – while she's distracted!
Baa.
Baa-pisce!
You saved us there, Yui.
Here we go. Are you feeling it? Wake up and smell the idols.
We'll dreameeh our way into BoyPara, no matter what!
And in the middle of my brother's show,
I'll show these dream-baa-rrassing photos to everyone!
Oh no!
Those drums open a BoyPara concert!
Huh?
Hurry up, baa!
Totally thanks for waiting!
The performance of BoyPara's totally popular idols WITH
is totally starting.
Asahi!
Koyoi!
Shougo!
WITH!
WITH! You're too hot to handle!
Really? This is totally real? Real, totally?
So this is Baa-oyPara...
But I can't see the stage at all, baa.
From a sunrise...
...to night stars yonder...
...together we can show you it all!
WITH!
Okay – let's go!
Gleaming Galactic Tightrope!
The two clock hands overlap
tokei no hari ga futatsu majiwaru
Heralding the dawn of a new world
aratanaru sekai ga hajimaru
Breathe in time with me and you'll see
kokyuu wo awasete saa
Now, are you ready?
kakugo wa dekita kai?
The fear of tomorrow on your trembling lips
ashita ni obieteiru kuchibiru
Astride a shooting star, inflamed
nagareboshi ni noseta chouhatsu
My heart starts pounding
mune ga sawagidashitara
As we dance in the hall of the cosmos
uchuu no dansuhooru
Don't stray from the path (Now I think)
fumihazusu na yo koko kara (honto wa)
Lean on my shoulder (We're on the brink)
tayotte ii yo ore ni wa (setogiwa)
They're so wonderful, baa...
Your cool façade will slip soon enough
yoyuushakushaku na kao datte ima no uchi
Incredible.
I can see right through to your
mou barebare da ze kimi no
Hmph. Your facade's gonna slip soon enough.
Prism Galaxy
prism galaxy
Here I dreameeh!
On the gleaming galactic tightrope
gira gyarachikku taitoroopu
Don't fall into the trap
damasarenai ze torappu
Rolling-rolling-rolling!
It's a lie, and it hit me
uso da yo gutto kita yo
That's the stuff! Gives my muscles that sexy feeling!
Beyond my dreams
yume no kanata
You and me adrift
kimi to ore tomadoi
Baa.
No trinity reflected in our eyes
hitomi ni utsuranu torinitii
Baa... Baa!
We're connected
seizasu no you ni
Yui! Baa!
Like a star chart
tsunagatta
That idiot! What's she doing up there?
On the gleaming galactic tightrope
gira gyarachikku taitoroopu
A single step could be deadly
kiken sugiru suteppu
Hey, no way...
You'll get ensnared
kimi wo makizoete
He... Help drea-me!
And if we start dancing
odoridashitara
Through morn and night
asa to naku aa yoru to naku
Oh man, what do I do?
To the edge of the galaxy
ginga no hate datte
She's going to fall!
I'll be with you
be with you
What do we do?
There's not much time to plan.
For crying out loud...
Come on, Megaboys!
At your service!
D-Dreameeh...
A blazing meteor streaks the sky
moenagara ochiteiku meteoru
Dreameeh!
Sorry, but I can't just let it pass by
nogashite wa yarenai yo ainiku
Hey, guys!
Heat it up down there, hot as this wool coat!
So tell me, how are you feeling now?
kibun wa dou dai naa
Come on now, I'm begging you
sorosoro tanomu ze
Nice!
You're rocking the sheep-coat look, dude!
Those three little words on the tip of my tongue
shita no ue de korogasu aishiteru
Baa! Wear me as a coat too!
I can't hold back the passion inside
jouzu ni kakushikirenai jounetsu
Man, I can't live without WITH!
I try to play it cool, but I keep glancing up
sumashita furi chirachira
Wow! Everyone's so excited to see me!
As we dance under the starlit disco ball
kousei no miraabooru
I can't hold back anymore – is this your game? (Now I think)
jirettai daro waza to sa (honto wa)
Wha– hey! What gives?
I know you understand, so don't complain (We'll get in sync)
kizuiten daro dame da na (dou ka na)
I wanna shock you, gotta reach out and grab your hand
kimi ni shock shock doushita tte te ni iretai
I can't take it, I need your
mou taerarenai ze give me your
Prism Galaxy
prism galaxy
Gripping tight in the night of romance
girigiri naito romanchikku
Let's dive right on into the dance
tobikonde yo massugu
It's a lie? No, it's time to believe
uso da yo shinjite yo
Baa, baa!
It's the power of love
ai no chikara
Baa!
It's a battle of wills with no retreat
owarinaki kakehiki
You and me bound by gravity
shibareten da guravitii
Dreameeh!
This must be fate
kore koso unmei
Dreameeh! Dreameeh! Dreameeh! Dreameeh!
And we're caught together
hikiatta
Dreameeh...
Gripping tight in the night of romance
girigiri naito romanchikku
Dream?
Whispers echo in the cosmic trance
taiyoukei no goshippu
I'm so glad you're safe.
I'm calling now, enticing you
kimi wo izanatte
Cyalume Time!
I've slipped through your defences
nukegakeshitara
And subtly, ah, bit by bit
sore to naku aa sarigenaku
Into a forbidden relationship
kindan no kankei e
I'm falling with you
falling with you
Nice! Nice! Nice! Nice!
Keep it coming, Asahi!
Whisper sweet nothings to me, Koyoi!
Shougo!
I'll teach that jerk to kick me like a ball!
That was amazing!
He saved you and got the audience even more excited!
Make sure every guest has a total blast every time.
That's the spirit of BoyPara.
Give them a blast every time...
Wait...
Meganii, why are you here?
Who's that?
He's the man in charge of Parajuku's PriPara!
As a matter of fact, I'm pulling double duty
being in charge of this BoyPara too.
Nice! Nice! Nice! Nice!
Totally Rockin'
Congratulations!
WITH's idol rank has risen to Totally Rockin'!
All right!
PriPara
BoyPara
We're gonna head over to PriPara now.
PriPara
BoyPara
Thanks a bunch for today!
No, thank you.
It's not every day you see theatrics like that.
See you later, got it?
So what were you trying to do before, anyway?
Well, more importantly, it really dreamed me.
I know how to put on a show
that gets PriPara more excited.
Make sure they have a total blast every time.
It's not just putting on a dreamy-cute show.
I've gotta work hard to make the concerts a real blast!
My Idol Time's filled up!
Puni.
Punicorn!
Scan the appropriate number
of My Tickets for your outfit.
Countdown to Idol Time!
The blue sky spreading across the outfit
is as clear and bright as Miss Yui's feelings!
And the vivid pink stands out beautifully!
Magical Star Pink Ensemble!
Start!
Miss Yui!
Dreamy-cute!
Hey, everyone!
From sunrise to night stars, and under midday sun,
won't you dreamy-cute with me?
Today I want you all to have a real blast!
Tick-tock magicalun-lun - Idol Time starts now!
chikutaku magica runrun aidoru taimu sutaato
Come on!
kamon
(Magical! Idol! Here we go!)
(majikaru aidoru here we go)
It's the magic girls long for
onna no ko ga akogaretekita mahou
A splendorous world where mysteries abound
fushigi wa joushiki chouisekai
I cast my spell and it's showtime
tonaetara shoutaimu
All I need is a little transformation and I'm ready
henshin shitara junbi bacchiri da yo
I feel like Cinderella
marude kibun wa shinderera
Beckoned secretly to the ball
kossori goshoutai
I'd better hurry up, cause everyone's waiting - no, no more limits
sore ja isogou minna matteru kitto anrimiteddo
Now the future is boundless
saa mirai eigou
Mark this moment in time!
toki o kizamu yo
(Tick-tock magical go!)
(chikutaku magikaru go)
Now hold on just a moment? I can't stop! Here, with my mic in hand
chotto jasutamoomen tomaranai yo maiku katate ni
Taking the hour hand and dancing, my heart singing
tanshin to dancing kokoro singing
In a thrilling singularity
tokimeki shingyuraritii
The mystery of the unclear is so entrancing
katachi no nai mono koso itsudatte hoshii yo
Music holds my hopes, so pretty and sweet
kibou to myuujikku puriti kyuuti
When I'm so excited I can't hold still
dokidoki machikirenai nara
Tick-tock magicalun-lun - it's Idol Time, and we're not done!
chikutaku magica runrun aidoru taimu tsuzuku yo
Is it a dream or reflection, truth or illusion? Who can say?
yume ka utsusu ka uso ka hontou ka dare mo wakaranai
Making Drama, switch on!
Adrift in the ebb and flow of time and space
watashi dake jikan fuuyuu kuukan
Until eternal twilight blooms
towairaito ga terasu made
Like a dream, dreamy-cute!
Tick-tock super Idol Time!
chikutaku super idol time
Tick and tock and
chii-ku ta-ku
Now just a moment, I hold my secrets always in my heart
jasutamoomen zutto zutto himitsu o mune ni
Whee!
In the loveliest outfit, in a single breath
saikou no koode wanburesu de
It's dreamcredible: welcome to dreamland!
Awakened by dream energy
mezameru doriimu enajii
Dreamy-cute Magical Clock Land!
The mystery of the unclear is so entrancing
katachi no nai mono koso itsudatte hoshii yo
Music holds my hopes, so pretty and sweet
kibou to myuujikku puriti kyuuti
Cyalume Time!
When I'm so excited I can't hold still
dokidoki machikirenai nara
Tick tock, I've gotta take it
chikutaku ima toraete
That chance comes just the once!
chansu wa isshun dake yo
Dreamy-cute!
Tick-tock magicalun-lun, now Idol Time: da capo!
chikutaku magica runrun aidoru taimu da kaapo
What a blast! This is so much fun!
Yeah! I think I like PriPara even more now!
It'd be too embarrassing to debut...
But maybe someday!
Nicely done!
What filled up Miss Yui's Idol Time today
was learning the importance of making
your fans have fun from studying BoyPara!
You can forget that feeling sometimes.
I wouldn't dream so far as saying
Shougo's show helped me.
Let's keep it up and make the
Grand Prix in June a dreaming success!
Yay!
That's rad –
a girl idol!
That's totally rad!
That's your little sister, right?
I hope you're supporting her.
Stuff that.
For crying out... first she interrupts our show,
then she rips off my emcee bit.
Master Shougo,
there's a delivery from your younger sister.
Looks like she feels bad about it.
Hey, what is it? I wanna see!
Well, well. Maybe she has grown up a bit.
What the heck is this?!
Shougo.
Oh, and she left a message.
"I'll let you off dreamily this time," she says.
She'll what?
I'm not letting her off –
not in a million dreaming years!
Next Episode
Let's book a spot on PriPara TV!
Okay! It'll be the perfect chance
to show off PriPara's dreaminess!
Capisce!
And our special guest is Sophie the Divine Idol!
That cool princess of SoLaMi SMILE?!
Just a moment, Lala. I'm on my way.
Um, so where are you, Sophie?
Pushu...
Yes, I wonder where I am...
Oh, jeez!
Next time, Sophie's Come to Cool!
Sophie's Come to Cool!
Come on, everyone! It's time to be an idol!