Huff, puff, yo!
Huff, puff... huh?
Here are some sandwiches –
please help out the track club!
Here's a hotdog!
Please lend the softball club a hand with our match too!
Please take this melon bread.
Melon bread from the basketball club!
We'll give you yakisoba bread!
Cheeseburger here!
You got it!
So I'm helping the track club,
and there's the softball club's match...
What other clubs need helpin'?
PriPara needs you to make your idol debut!
And making my idol debut in PriPara...
Hey! That ain't sports – no marks!
Aw, come on, you're helping out every other club.
Why can'tcha dream us a hand too?
There's a fashion studio now and stuff!
It's so much fun!
No marks, yo!
I ain't interested in idols!
Huff, puff, yo! Huff, puff...
Aw, it didn't work.
And there's only one more week
until the Idol Time Grand Prix...
Don't throw in the dream!
Lala, don't think "only one week" –
it's "we've got a whole week"!
Capisce!
Today could be the day someone
finally appears and makes their debut!
Yo, I Became A Helper Idol!
Huff, puff, yo!
Yui and Lala's passion for idols is the real deal.
That tennis match I teamed up
with them for really fired me up.
I realised idols weren't lifeless.
But I've still got sports.
Flyers, flyers!
Gracias, gracias!
Flyers, flyers, gracias!
Please take one, everyone!
Hey, that's the boys' dorm's building manager.
Jogging, are we? Got a tune and a spring in your step!
'Sup, Babario. What're ya giving out there?
Our old shopping arcade hasn't been too lively lately,
so I put together a plan to put it desper-ight-o!
For those with concentration! Iron Cup-and-Ball Competition
Bring your old slippers from home! Slipper Skating Competition
How are your inner muscles? See how you stack up!
For those with concentration! Iron Cup-and-Ball Competition
Bring your old slippers from home! Slipper Skating Competition
How are your inner muscles? See how you stack up!
"Invisible Musical Chairs Competition"
Surging in popularity, it's the "That's How It Goes!" Karuta Competition
Get hit and you're out! "Paintball Game"
When     June 3rd (Saturday)
Where     Paparajuku Shopping Arcade
Who         Everyone from kids to elderly
When     June 3rd (Saturday)
Where     Paparajuku Shopping Arcade
Who         Everyone from kids to elderly
Events
Paparajuku Town
Sports Game Competition
Opening a stall
is free ! !
"Invisible Musical Chairs Competition"
Surging in popularity, it's the "That's How It Goes!" Karuta Competition
Get hit and you're out! "Paintball Game"
Opening a stall
"Invisible Musical Chairs Competition"
Surging in popularity, it's the "That's How It Goes!" Karuta Competition
Get hit and you're out! "Paintball Game"
Opening a stall
"Invisible Musical Chairs Competition"
Surging in popularity, it's the "That's How It Goes!" Karuta Competition
Get hit and you're out! "Paintball Game"
Opening a stall
"Invisible Musical Chairs Competition"
Surging in popularity, it's the "That's How It Goes!" Karuta Competition
Get hit and you're out! "Paintball Game"
Opening a stall
"Invisible Musical Chairs Competition"
Surging in popularity, it's the "That's How It Goes!" Karuta Competition
Get hit and you're out! "Paintball Game"
Opening a stall
"Invisible Musical Chairs Competition"
Surging in popularity, it's the "That's How It Goes!" Karuta Competition
Get hit and you're out! "Paintball Game"
Opening a stall
"Invisible Musical Chairs Competition"
Surging in popularity, it's the "That's How It Goes!" Karuta Competition
Get hit and you're out! "Paintball Game"
Opening a stall
"Invisible Musical Chairs Competition"
Surging in popularity, it's the "That's How It Goes!" Karuta Competition
Get hit and you're out! "Paintball Game"
Opening a stall
"Invisible Musical Chairs Competition"
Surging in popularity, it's the "That's How It Goes!" Karuta Competition
Get hit and you're out! "Paintball Game"
Opening a stall
"Invisible Musical Chairs Competition"
Surging in popularity, it's the "That's How It Goes!" Karuta Competition
Get hit and you're out! "Paintball Game"
Opening a stall
"Invisible Musical Chairs Competition"
Surging in popularity, it's the "That's How It Goes!" Karuta Competition
Get hit and you're out! "Paintball Game"
Opening a stall
"Invisible Musical Chairs Competition"
Surging in popularity, it's the "That's How It Goes!" Karuta Competition
Get hit and you're out! "Paintball Game"
Opening a stall
"Invisible Musical Chairs Competition"
Surging in popularity, it's the "That's How It Goes!" Karuta Competition
Get hit and you're out! "Paintball Game"
Opening a stall
"Invisible Musical Chairs Competition"
Surging in popularity, it's the "That's How It Goes!" Karuta Competition
Get hit and you're out! "Paintball Game"
Opening a stall
"Invisible Musical Chairs Competition"
Surging in popularity, it's the "That's How It Goes!" Karuta Competition
Get hit and you're out! "Paintball Game"
Opening a stall
"Invisible Musical Chairs Competition"
Surging in popularity, it's the "That's How It Goes!" Karuta Competition
Get hit and you're out! "Paintball Game"
Opening a stall
"Invisible Musical Chairs Competition"
Surging in popularity, it's the "That's How It Goes!" Karuta Competition
Get hit and you're out! "Paintball Game"
Opening a stall
"Invisible Musical Chairs Competition"
Surging in popularity, it's the "That's How It Goes!" Karuta Competition
Get hit and you're out! "Paintball Game"
Opening a stall
"Invisible Musical Chairs Competition"
Surging in popularity, it's the "That's How It Goes!" Karuta Competition
Get hit and you're out! "Paintball Game"
Opening a stall
"Invisible Musical Chairs Competition"
Surging in popularity, it's the "That's How It Goes!" Karuta Competition
Get hit and you're out! "Paintball Game"
Opening a stall
"Invisible Musical Chairs Competition"
Surging in popularity, it's the "That's How It Goes!" Karuta Competition
Get hit and you're out! "Paintball Game"
Opening a stall
"Invisible Musical Chairs Competition"
Surging in popularity, it's the "That's How It Goes!" Karuta Competition
Get hit and you're out! "Paintball Game"
Opening a stall
"Invisible Musical Chairs Competition"
Surging in popularity, it's the "That's How It Goes!" Karuta Competition
Get hit and you're out! "Paintball Game"
Opening a stall
"Invisible Musical Chairs Competition"
Surging in popularity, it's the "That's How It Goes!" Karuta Competition
Get hit and you're out! "Paintball Game"
Opening a stall
"Invisible Musical Chairs Competition"
Surging in popularity, it's the "That's How It Goes!" Karuta Competition
Get hit and you're out! "Paintball Game"
Opening a stall
"Invisible Musical Chairs Competition"
Surging in popularity, it's the "That's How It Goes!" Karuta Competition
Get hit and you're out! "Paintball Game"
Opening a stall
"Invisible Musical Chairs Competition"
Surging in popularity, it's the "That's How It Goes!" Karuta Competition
Get hit and you're out! "Paintball Game"
Opening a stall
"Invisible Musical Chairs Competition"
Surging in popularity, it's the "That's How It Goes!" Karuta Competition
Get hit and you're out! "Paintball Game"
Opening a stall
"Invisible Musical Chairs Competition"
Surging in popularity, it's the "That's How It Goes!" Karuta Competition
Get hit and you're out! "Paintball Game"
Opening a stall
"Invisible Musical Chairs Competition"
Surging in popularity, it's the "That's How It Goes!" Karuta Competition
Get hit and you're out! "Paintball Game"
Opening a stall
"Invisible Musical Chairs Competition"
Surging in popularity, it's the "That's How It Goes!" Karuta Competition
Get hit and you're out! "Paintball Game"
Opening a stall
"Invisible Musical Chairs Competition"
Surging in popularity, it's the "That's How It Goes!" Karuta Competition
Get hit and you're out! "Paintball Game"
Opening a stall
"Invisible Musical Chairs Competition"
Surging in popularity, it's the "That's How It Goes!" Karuta Competition
Get hit and you're out! "Paintball Game"
Opening a stall
"Invisible Musical Chairs Competition"
Surging in popularity, it's the "That's How It Goes!" Karuta Competition
Get hit and you're out! "Paintball Game"
Opening a stall
"Invisible Musical Chairs Competition"
Surging in popularity, it's the "That's How It Goes!" Karuta Competition
Get hit and you're out! "Paintball Game"
Opening a stall
"Invisible Musical Chairs Competition"
Surging in popularity, it's the "That's How It Goes!" Karuta Competition
Get hit and you're out! "Paintball Game"
Opening a stall
"Invisible Musical Chairs Competition"
Surging in popularity, it's the "That's How It Goes!" Karuta Competition
Get hit and you're out! "Paintball Game"
Opening a stall
"Invisible Musical Chairs Competition"
Surging in popularity, it's the "That's How It Goes!" Karuta Competition
Get hit and you're out! "Paintball Game"
Opening a stall
"Invisible Musical Chairs Competition"
Surging in popularity, it's the "That's How It Goes!" Karuta Competition
Get hit and you're out! "Paintball Game"
Opening a stall
"Invisible Musical Chairs Competition"
Surging in popularity, it's the "That's How It Goes!" Karuta Competition
Get hit and you're out! "Paintball Game"
Opening a stall
"Invisible Musical Chairs Competition"
Surging in popularity, it's the "That's How It Goes!" Karuta Competition
Get hit and you're out! "Paintball Game"
Opening a stall
"Invisible Musical Chairs Competition"
Surging in popularity, it's the "That's How It Goes!" Karuta Competition
Get hit and you're out! "Paintball Game"
Opening a stall
"Invisible Musical Chairs Competition"
Surging in popularity, it's the "That's How It Goes!" Karuta Competition
Get hit and you're out! "Paintball Game"
Opening a stall
"Invisible Musical Chairs Competition"
Surging in popularity, it's the "That's How It Goes!" Karuta Competition
Get hit and you're out! "Paintball Game"
Opening a stall
"Invisible Musical Chairs Competition"
Surging in popularity, it's the "That's How It Goes!" Karuta Competition
Get hit and you're out! "Paintball Game"
Opening a stall
"Invisible Musical Chairs Competition"
Surging in popularity, it's the "That's How It Goes!" Karuta Competition
Get hit and you're out! "Paintball Game"
Opening a stall
"Invisible Musical Chairs Competition"
Surging in popularity, it's the "That's How It Goes!" Karuta Competition
Get hit and you're out! "Paintball Game"
Opening a stall
"Invisible Musical Chairs Competition"
Surging in popularity, it's the "That's How It Goes!" Karuta Competition
Get hit and you're out! "Paintball Game"
Opening a stall
"Invisible Musical Chairs Competition"
Surging in popularity, it's the "That's How It Goes!" Karuta Competition
Get hit and you're out! "Paintball Game"
Opening a stall
"Invisible Musical Chairs Competition"
Surging in popularity, it's the "That's How It Goes!" Karuta Competition
Get hit and you're out! "Paintball Game"
Opening a stall
"Invisible Musical Chairs Competition"
Surging in popularity, it's the "That's How It Goes!" Karuta Competition
Get hit and you're out! "Paintball Game"
Opening a stall
"Invisible Musical Chairs Competition"
Surging in popularity, it's the "That's How It Goes!" Karuta Competition
Get hit and you're out! "Paintball Game"
Opening a stall
If you didn't know, I'm also chairman
of the neighbourhood association!
"Invisible Musical Chairs Competition"
Surging in popularity, it's the "That's How It Goes!" Karuta Competition
Get hit and you're out! "Paintball Game"
Opening a stall
"Invisible Musical Chairs Competition"
Surging in popularity, it's the "That's How It Goes!" Karuta Competition
Get hit and you're out! "Paintball Game"
Opening a stall
"Invisible Musical Chairs Competition"
Surging in popularity, it's the "That's How It Goes!" Karuta Competition
Get hit and you're out! "Paintball Game"
Opening a stall
"Invisible Musical Chairs Competition"
Surging in popularity, it's the "That's How It Goes!" Karuta Competition
Get hit and you're out! "Paintball Game"
Opening a stall
"Invisible Musical Chairs Competition"
Surging in popularity, it's the "That's How It Goes!" Karuta Competition
Get hit and you're out! "Paintball Game"
Opening a stall
"Invisible Musical Chairs Competition"
Surging in popularity, it's the "That's How It Goes!" Karuta Competition
Get hit and you're out! "Paintball Game"
Opening a stall
You're a sports lover, domingo, my amigo.
Ergo, after school, to the shopping arcade you go!
No foolin'.
Sounds pretty cool!
Looks like there's some kind of event
happening at the Paparajuku shopping arcade.
I've been so busy since moving here
that I haven't had a chance to go!
It looks fun!
But we need to focus on finding
someone to debut in PriPara.
Hold up.
Yakisoba
Takoyaki
Chocolate Bananas
Rice Balls,
Participants, please inform Babario in advance
Inquiries: Babario
Yakisoba
Takoyaki
Chocolate Bananas
Rice Balls,
Participants, please inform Babario in advance
Inquiries: Babario
For those with concentration! Iron Cup-and-Ball Competition
Bring your old slippers from home! Slipper Skating Competition
How are you inner muscles? See how you stack up!
"Invisible Musical Chairs Competition"
Surging in popularity, it's the "That's How It Goes!" Karuta Competition
Get hit and you're out! "Paintball Game"
For those with concentration! Iron Cup-and-Ball Competition
Bring your old slippers from home! Slipper Skating Competition
How are you inner muscles? See how you stack up!
"Invisible Musical Chairs Competition"
Surging in popularity, it's the "That's How It Goes!" Karuta Competition
Get hit and you're out! "Paintball Game"
Opening a stall
is free ! !
Events
Who      Everyone from kids to elderly
For those with concentration! Iron Cup-and-Ball Competition
Surging in popularity, it's the "That's How It Goes!" Karuta Competition
It says here that anyone can dream along and enter!
Yakisoba
Takoyaki
Chocolate Bananas
Participants, please inform Babario in advance
Get hit and you're out! "Paintball Game"
Surging in popularity, it's the "That's How It Goes!" Karuta Competition
We should set up a showroom to promote PriPara!
That's a great idea!
All right! Let's hop to it, not a second to dream!
Capisce!
Pa-para, pa-para pa-para!
Papara-ju!
Sho, sho-sho-sho-sho
sho-sho, sho-shopping
Arcade!
Today's big event is now...
Underway!
Come on, my little buddies –
you're in the prime of your youth!
From the Showa idols' platinum generation,
your neighbourhood association chairman Babario
presents the Paparajuku Sports Competition!
Iron Cup-and-Ball
Competition
Slipper Skating
Invisible Musical Chairs Competition
We've borrowed the various shops
to set up game corners
Invisible Musical Chairs Competition
"That's How It Goes!"
Karuta Competition
Invisible Musical Chairs Competition
which will be a desper-ight joy to young and old!
Paintball
Competition
Invisible Musical Chairs Competition
Bien-ing now!
Dreamy!
It's looking pretty lively.
Well, hey. You two're participating too?
Hey, Nino!
Sure, we'll be participating.
But we're also opening a shop ourselves
to try and dream up some idols!
You don't say. You're passionate as ever, huh?
Come check us out, Nino.
I'm sure you'll start dreaming about debuting yourself!
I already told ya – this here Nino's only into sports.
Here I come!
We're taking' this energy right to the top!
Nino really is something.
She took first place in invisible musical chairs too.
Come get 'em while they're cheap!
We've got freshly-made steaming-hot rice balls here!
I'll have one, please!
Me too!
All right! We're a huge hit!
Lala, we need three more!
Capisce!
So we're supposed to be, like, a PriPara showroom,
but we're basically just selling rice balls here.
Excuse me! One for me too here!
You got it!
My plan's working like a dream!
With this dreamlike crowd of customers,
it's the perfect chance!
We're now starting a dreamyful campaign!
For all girls making their idol debuts,
you'll receive not ten, not fifty,
but a hundred free rice balls!
Seriously? That'd be so embarrassing!
The world's truly gone to ruin.
And girls only? Totally unfair.
Let's go.
You couldn't even eat that many.
Dreamy bummer.
They all kinda left.
Seems you're having a bit of trouble, huh?
Dream?
Huh?
Nino here's on an all-out winning streak!
Well, why don't you try getting first place at idoling too?
I'll dream you some free rice balls if you do!
No marks!
Cause I'm all about bread!
Shee ya!
Wait a dream!
Yui.
At this stage, our last hope is the athletic Nino!
Yeah! We'll have to get one over on her
so we can dream her into PriPara!
Now what game should I challenge next?
Sports
"That's How It Goes!"
Karuta Competition
Sports
"That's How It Goes!"
Karuta Competition
A sports "That's How It Goes!" karuta competition...
Looks pretty hot!
What this person's deal?
"That's how it goes"...
On a rainy day, running laps in the gymnasium...
O
Here I come!
Yo, too easy!
Water from the drinking fountain
is extra tasty after practice...
Heya!
W
Nino! Nino! Go for it, yeah!
This game's gonna be a piece of cake too!
Eating bananas before a match to boost your nutrition...
All right!
E
Not half bad.
I acknowledge your skill at "That's How It Goes!" karuta.
But now, for you and I...
The Gloves Are Off
The gloves are off!
Bring it on!
This is getting quite heated.
I just let my guard down before.
I ain't gonna lose!
Calling the director nicknames when he's not around.
Moustachioed Dandy
Gentleman
Buddah
Gramps
Devoted Husband
C
Heya!
Too slow!
C
Flash of a Blade
Taken in the flash of a blade.
This round goes to me too.
Y-You haven't beat me yet!
N-Next time I'm going all out!
I'm taking it for sure!
Concentrate, yo...
Gotta bring out my full power.
Sharpen all of my instincts to a keen edge...
Be–
B
Being scouted by the volleyball
and basketball teams due to being tall!
B
Way to go, mystery girl! She's so strong!
No way!
It was a total shutout.
A titanic struggle.
It was a good match.
Wait up!
Who...
Who are you?
Toudou Shion.
I'm an idol on a journey to hone my spirit.
You're... an idol?
Yet my name is not worth giving.
I hear my next trial calling me.
Farewell.
That was a total shutout.
Toudou Shion...
I swear I'll become as strong as you are one day!
So lovely to meet-ador so many of you here today!
Babario has a desper-right important announcement!
It's time for the competition's highlight:
the paintball contest is about to bien!
Let mia see you all enter!
I bet Nino will dream her way into this too!
Let's check it out!
This game is played with paintball guns.
If you're hit, you're out straight away!
Are...
...you...
...se...
...ri...
...ous?
Battles and love are equally harsh and unforgiving.
You got that right!
Dosu...
koi.
My winning streak may have been broken,
but ain't letting that happen again!
Punicorn...
Puni... corn.
Punicorn!
Pu?
Punicorn?
Nino! Dream at us!
If we win, you're gonna debut for us!
You two sure don't know when to quit!
Here I dream! A dreamy-cute shot!
A capisce shot!
Didn't even have to dodge!
Here I come!
You ready to give up, or what?
Never give up!
That's the motto we dream by!
We're as clingy and tenacious as natto!
No matter where you Ji-go-ku...
the walls and the doors both have ears.
Jigoku Mimiko stands above you!
Dream?!
H-Head Disciplinarian?
I heard it quite clearly.
You've not learned at all, and you're still
trying to court female idols, aren't you?
Say what? Would we do that?
No way! I wouldn't dream of it!
Oh, well, if you do say so.
Then why don't you try placing
these microphones at your feet?
Dream!
For an idol, placing your microphone
down in front of you means retiring.
If idols are worth nothing to you,
you'll have no problem doing so.
Why don't you give it a try?
I know it doesn't actually mean I have to retire,
but I still really don't want to do it.
But maybe this mic...
was handmade by a member of the old generation
of microphone craftsmen, Mr Jackson!
Mr Jackson lives in the Palps mountain range,
putting his heart and dreams
into the microphones he crafts.
But his son Douglas told him his era had passed,
and he ran away from home!
But even so, Mr Jackson holds onto hopes and dreams
of Douglas one day coming back to him!
I can't turn my back on the microphone Mr Jackson made
and give up on being an idol – I couldn't dream of it!
Uh... Yui, are you daydreaming again?
If I hold this microphone while dreaming my heart out,
I'm sure Douglas will come back as well!
I knew it! The rot of idols runs into your very heart!
On mimiko-mmand, destroy them utterly!
Hold up!
Ganging up's no marks!
Douglas! You came back to us!
Oi! That's Nino!
Here I come!
Come on, while they're distracted!
Dreamy-cute!
Capisce!
Lala!
Even if I can see nothing,
my ears left and right can track you
wherever you Ji-go-ku!
Like right there!
Douglas, look out!
Yui!
D-Douglas...
Preparing...
delicious rice...
and crafting microphones...
are one...
and the same.
Yui?
Nino here...
Well, I'm not Douglas.
Our names aren't even slightly similar.
But your passionate words lit a fire in my heart!
I see you!
At this rate...
Nino!
Take this!
Nino, mega-comin' at you!
I could hear
the sound of something striking me straight on.
Game over-io de Janeiro!
The winner is Señorita Nino!
Nino, Nino, you're the winner!
Nino, Nino, victory!
Nino, congratulations on wining!
Couldn't have done it without my pals.
Moving my whole body like that feels great, yo!
You can move around like crazy
in an idol performance too!
Nino, you should totally try debuting!
Yui and Lala, idols really get you passionate.
What exactly is this PriPara thing?
Well...
It's a world full of dreams and excitement,
all sparkling and amazing!
Honour students, harmony-seekers,
thrill-seekers, devils and angels!
PriPara's a place where anyone
can be a wonderful idol, no matter who they are!
Anyone...
No matter who...
Like that girl...
Or Lala...
Or Yui.
Okay, Nino here's gonna try debuting!
Capisce!
Wait, what?
You mean it? No dreaming?
Your idol souls have won me over.
And besides, there's someone
I have to avenge myself against!
We dreaming did it!
And this means we can hold the Idol Time Grand Prix!
But do you have a PriTicket?
Well, sure! I got one those too!
I figured it'd be good for keeping crows
out of the rubbish.
Anti-bird
netting
I'll run and get it!
Well, that's a shock.
This place is totally empty!
Welcome to Prism Stone.
May I have you name?
I'm Nijiiro Nino, yo!
Well then, Miss Nino, I'll register your stage outfit.
Let's see...
I think the sporty new Pop brand
Neon Drop would suit you perfectly!
That's awesome! A new brand!
Neon Drop...
Here I come!
PriPara Change!
Cheers!
This is totally full marks!
Suits me to a T, and it's easy to move in to boot!
You look great!
You look dreamcredible!
Miss Nino, please take this.
I'm sure it's from helping out
Miss Yui and Miss Lala earlier.
Your Idol Time has been maxed out!
That's amazing! Way to go, Nino!
Thank you v'much!
Puni-puni.
Dream?
Hey, Punicorn's holding an egg.
Puni... corn!
Chuppe!
Dream!
It's a mascot!
Chuppe chuppe chuppe!
Who's this little guy?
Hey, that tickles!
No way! Is he gonna be your manager already?
Chuppe!
All right! The brakes are off –
time for my first-ever show!
Chuppe... Chuppe!
Scan the appropriate number
of My Tickets for your outfit.
You can also scan each other's Friend Tickets.
Countdown to Idol Time!
The new brand Neon Drop is a perfect fit
for the universal sports-lover Miss Nino.
This baseball uniform has been
reimagined as a stage outfit!
Baseball Game Ensemble!
Startin'!
Miss Nino, Neon Drop looks wonderful on you!
Helter-skelter - ready, go!
accha koccha ready go
Come on!
come on
Performing really uses the whole body!
My arms, legs and hips are lovin' it!
Moving my body's what I love the most!
Play ball!
play ball
Now it's summer, summertime, she who moves first strikes a hit tune
summer summer summertime sente hisshou hitto chuun
Here come the helper, ready to rumble
sukketo sanjou kokkara ga honban da
I'm gonna be number one, and you can bet I'll walk the walk
number number number one mezasou yuugen jikkou
I pick up the rhythm and then it's one, two, three and
rizumu wo kanjitottara isseeno de
Commands input straight into my heart, now I'm ready, go
kokoro komando nyuuryoku wo ready go
Circle, cross, triangle, I'll square with you, so mark my words
maru batsu sankaku shikaku sankaku
There's no need to get marked off
sanka shikaku da nante no iranai yo
'Cause when you're here, we're all friends
koko ni kitara minna tomodachi
Good fences make good neighbours ('Sup!)
shitashiki naka de atte mo reigi wo (chassu)
And you gotta respect both friends and rivals (Let's go!)
mikata ni mo teki ni mo keii wo haraou (sharassu)
You know if you hold back (If you hold back?)
tekagen shitara (shitara)
You're disqualified (You're out!)
sokkoku taijou (auto)
Here I come, with my full power
zenryoku de iku yo saa
So see if you can keep up
kakugo kimete tsuikite ne
Three, two, one... go!
three two one go
It's helter-skelter! Get up, get up and play the game!
whoa accha koccha get up get up play the game
You're dancing before you even realise
karada ga katte ni odoridashite
Out of control, no slowing down
seigyo fukanou tomerarenai yo
Our strategy's going by instinct
senryaku wa mochiron kankaku
It's helter-skelter! Get up, get up and play the game!
accha koccha get up get up purei the game
Here I come!
Glitch out all your wimpiness (Hop to it!)
okubyou na jibun wo bagurasechatte (ikkee)
Making Drama, switch on!
My heart's pounding so much it feels like it'll burst
bakubaku takanatta kono mune no naka nara
Beep-boop!
My brain's all scrambled up (Yay!)
sukuranburu joutai (yay)
Comin' at ya!
Live it up! This rocks!
live it up saikou jan
Let's play Idol Time!
let's play idol time
Yeah, come on now and ride that player's high
whoa motto motto zutto zutto player's high
Feel like shouting it right from the heart
hontou no kimochi ga sakebigoe
Poppin' Bit Scramble!
We'll be earnest, burning with ardour
shoujiki ni narou atsukunarou yo
That's how it's gotta be for me
watashi nara mochiron
I'm havin' a blast, yo!
That's a high score!
Helter-skelter - ready, go!
accha koccha ready go
It's helter-skelter! Get up, get up and play the game!
whoa accha koccha get up get up play the game
Cyalume Time!
You're dancing before you even realise
karada ga katte ni odoridashite
Out of control, no slowing down
seigyo fukanou tomerarenai yo
Our strategy's going by instinct
senryaku wa mochiron kankaku
Full marks!
It's helter-skelter! Get up, get up and play the game!
accha koccha get up get up purei the game
Glitch out all your wimpiness (Hop to it!)
okubyou na jibun wo bagurasechatte (ikkee)
My heart's pounding so much it feels like it'll burst
bakubaku takanatta kono mune no naka nara
The signal's all scrambled now (Yay!)
sukuranburu joutai (yay)
Live it up! This rocks!
live it up saikou jan
Let's play Idol Time!
let's play idol time
Congratulations on your first performance, Miss Nino!
You're stunning!
Nino, mega-comin' at you!
Nino, that was just dreamyful!
Chuppe...
Performing's pretty fun!
I reckon I'll keep at this idol thing!
Really?
Chuppe!
Punicorn!
I'm sure the Idol Grand Prix
on Sunday's going to be a smash hit now!
On Sunday?
I've got a softball game that day, so I can't make it.
What?
Dream?
What?!
Okono-
miyaki
Ninja-
Monja
Okonomiyaki
Ninja-Monja
That Shion!
Ever since she left on that journey of hers,
she hasn't come back to Parajuku once!
What's she even up to, anyway?
You're lonely without Shion around, aren't you?
Y-Yeah right, as if.
But we may as well go see her
if she's not coming back any time soon.
If you say so, Dorothy.
Next Episode
The Grand Prix's on the same day
as Nino's softball game!
This is a dreamsaster!
But we can't give up.
SoLaMi SMILE will handle the show
until Nino can win her match and dash over!
Not another step.
Head Disciplinarian?
No matter where you Ji-go-ku,
the walls and doors both have ears!
And, yes, on the pitch as well!
Jigoku Mimiko shall claim victory here!
What?
Next time, Pitch It! The Idol Time Grand Prix!
Pitch It!
The Idol Time Grand Prix!
Come on, everyone! It's time to be an idol!